welcome to category five technology TV
欢迎来到五类科技电视
this is episode number five 86 and this
这是集数 五笔 86，这
week we have got an Amazon echo dot
我们有一个亚马逊回声点
third-gen mm-hmm it's really a
第三代mm-hmm 它真的是一个
complicated name and we've got a Google
复杂的名字 ，我们有一个谷歌
home Mini and these two devices are
家用迷你和这两个设备
smart home devices that allow us to do
智能家居设备，使我们能够 做
things like turn on and off lights and
打开 和关闭灯 和
adjust our thermostat and also just be
调整我们的恒温器，也只是
able to tap into resources like finding
能够 利用 寻找等资源
the weather forecast just by asking a
天气预报只是问 一个
question of our devices but the question
我们的设备问题，但问题
becomes for us because they're the same
对 我们来说 因为 他们是一样的
price virtually and the same form factor
价格几乎和相同的外形
which one is gonna be best for me which
哪一个会 是最适合我这
one should I look at and so tonight we
我应该看一下，所以 今晚我们
set out to unbiased provide an unbiased
开始不偏不倚地提供一个不偏不倚的
review for you so that you can make that
为您审查，以便您可以做到这一点
decision based on the questions that
基于这些问题的决定
we're going to ask so I think we're
我们 要问 所以我认为我们是
gonna have a lot of fun tonight oh yeah
今晚会有很多 乐趣哦是的
do it so hey stick around we'll be right
做到这一点，嘿，坚持我们是对的
back this is category-five tech
这是第五类 技术
GTV our live recordings are trusted only
GTV我们的现场录音仅受信任
to solid-state drive by Kingston
金士顿的固态硬盘
technology revive your computer with
技术使您的计算机恢复活力
improved performance and reliability
提高了性能和 可靠性
over traditional hard drives with
超过传统的硬盘驱动器
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams live
金士顿SSD类5类电视直播
with Telestream wire cast and nimble
使用Telestream 线材铸造和灵活
streamer tune in every week on roku Kodi
roku Kodi每周都有流光调
Plex and other HLS video players for
Plex 和其他HLS视频播放器
local show times visit category 5 TV
当地时间表访问5类电视
category 5 TV is a member of the tech
5类电视是该技术的成员
podcast network if it's tech it's here
播客网络，如果它是 技术它在这里
cat 5 dot TV / TPM and the international
猫5点电视/ TPM和 国际
association of internet broadcasters cat
互联网广播公司 协会
5 dot TV slash ia IB and seen with that
5 点电视斜线ia IB和看到它
we throw away the scripts the rest of
我们扔掉 了剩下的脚本
the show is completely unscripted I knew
这节目完全没有脚本我 知道
that's where it's nice to have you here
这就是让你来到这里真好的地方
how is everybody doing good
每个人都做得好
I'm good I'm good good thank you
我很好我很好，谢谢你
nice to see you everybody tonight we're
很高兴见到 你今晚大家 我们
gonna be talking with and we've got a
会和我说话，我们有一个
couple of interviews tonight and we're
今晚几次采访 我们都是
really excited about this big big names
真的很兴奋这个 大牌明星
yeah huge we're gonna be talking with a
是的， 我们要和一个人说话
little miss from Allah I can't say it
安拉的小小想念我不能说出来
just yet we have a representative from
只是还没有，我们有从代表
said Amazon echo dot is here to join us
亚马逊回声点在这里 加入 我们
tonight we've also got Google home mini
今晚我们还有谷歌家迷你
here with us tonight we're gonna be
我们今晚和我们在一起
speaking with her and we're gonna be
跟她 说话 ， 我们会的
learning we're gonna finally be putting
学习我们 最终会放
to rest the question because we all have
我们都有这个问题
this question which one is better right
这个问题哪一个是 更好的 权利
which one's gonna be the one that does
哪一个会成为那个人
what I need it to do Jeff hold your
我需要它 做杰夫抱你的
tongue man hold your and some of us may
舌头男人抱着你和我们中的一些人可能
be like entirely against the the
完全违背了
automated home but all those of us who
自动化的家，但我们所有的人谁
are interested in the technology tonight
今晚 对 这项技术很感兴趣
we're gonna be talking with both of them
我们要和他们两个人谈谈
and seeing how each one responds to us
并了解每个人如何回应我们
and how they react so that's gonna be
以及 他们 如何 反应，因此会 是
that's gonna be a lot of fun
这会很有趣
what do you been up to this week this
这个 星期你做了什么？
week homework nothing but I just work
一周的作业，但我只是工作
pretty much work and work and homework
几乎是工作和工作以及家庭作业
any tech stuff well I'm learning how to
任何高科技的东西 好，我正在学习如何
use Google slides Google slides so this
使用谷歌幻灯片谷歌幻灯片这样
is their presentations aka PowerPoint
是他们的演讲，又名PowerPoint
for Google Drive right yeah okay so I
对于谷歌驱动器是的好，所以我
spent a lot of time learning how to put
花了很多时间学习如何放
audio on each slide is
每张幻灯片上的音频是
school is so cool so that you don't have
学校太酷了，所以你没有
to actually speak when you're presenting
当你出席时真正说话
a presentation okay define so you just
一个演示文稿好的定义所以你只是
record your voice you Rick oh you attach
记录你的声音Rick哦，你附上
it to the side yourself you record it
你记录它自己到一边
right computer mic or whatever yeah and
正确的电脑麦克风或其他什么是和
then you just click to the next slide
然后你只需点击 下 一张幻灯片
and then the next thing happens the
然后 接下来的事情就发生了
problem is I found out there is a
问题是我发现有 一个
problem if you're working in a group of
如果你 在一群 人中 工作的 问题
people yes you have to be on your Google
人们 是的， 你必须 在你的谷歌上
Drive the Google Drive like the main one
像主要驱动器一样驱动Google云端硬盘
so the one that created the slides share
使创建的幻灯片 分享
Drive you can't you can't put audio on
驱动你不能你 不能把音频打开
to like it all hot I can't have anybody
喜欢这一切都很热，我不能拥有任何人
else having an often on Lincoln I did
其他具有 经常 在林肯我做
that seems like a glaring speech is it
这似乎是一个明显的演讲
is it a permissions issue because I know
这是一个权限问题，因为我知道
if I share our Google Drive folder the
如果我分享我们的Google云端硬盘文件夹了
weekly show notes for the for this show
这个节目的每周节目笔记
and if I forget to put Jeff on the on
如果我忘 了把杰夫放在上面
the viewable list right he doesn't show
他没有展示的可见列表
access it then he can't see it right so
访问它然后他不能正确看到它
it to him from his perspective he
他从他的角度来看待 他
doesn't see this week's episode right
没有看到本周的情节
just sees the previous week's mm-hmm I
只看到前一周的mm-hmm 我
have to remember to add Jeff to that
必须记住将杰夫加入其中
right something like that like I hope so
就像我希望的那样
maybe it's a permissions thing maybe
也许这是权限的事情
because it seems like Google's really
因为它看起来像谷歌 真的
got the whole concept of right
得到了正确的整体概念
collaborative work I would think that
合作工作我会这么认为
would be a glaring future issue if they
如果他们是一个明显的未来问题
didn't allow it I know I don't know how
不允许它我知道我不知道如何
many people are doing a presentation on
很多 人都在做演讲
anemia people try to record themselves
贫血症的人试图记录自己
and stick it to a file and then share it
并将其粘贴到一个文件， 然后分享
with me it's kind of cool though it is
和我在一起虽然它很酷
that's really cool it's better for like
这真的很酷，对于喜欢更好
I don't mind so I don't mind speaking or
我不介意 所以我不 介意说话或
in front of people I don't mind
在 我不 介意 的 人 面前
presenting anything pretty much but I do
提出任何东西， 但我做
work amongst people who don't do it like
在那些不喜欢的 人中间工作
an amazing show every week and so
每周都有一场精彩的表演
they're nervous so I said oh I've got a
他们很紧张，所以我说哦，我有一个
great idea let's just record your voice
好主意 让我们只记录 你的声音
and then I'll get up there and I'll like
然后 我会在 那里 ，我会喜欢
go through the slides and your voices
浏览 幻灯片和你的声音
will be on there we tried it and that
我们 会 在那里尝试它
didn't work
没有工作
oh dear so now they're forced to be up
亲爱的，所以现在他们被迫了
with me at the front of you find that
和我在你 面前 找到那个
the the education sector and and the
教育 部门和
college system is
大学系统是
transitioning toward use of these
过渡到使用这些
technologies so that someone like
技术让 喜欢的人
yourself who is experienced working in a
你自己有经验 的人
studio environment
工作室环境
mm-hmm all of a sudden has an advantage
mm-hmm突然有一个优势
over other students because you're
因为你是 其他学生
presenting every single week here's the
每周都会出现在这里
thing
事情
I am legit the genius in the class and a
我是合法的类和天才
contact I react like that Jeff come on
联系我像 Jeff那样 反应 过来
that was genuine astonishment I don't
这真是让 我 惊讶不已
know I would try what I mean the amount
知道我会尝试我的意思是金额
of tech out there the fact that I would
那里的科技事实我会
have thought there would be more people
我以为会有更多的人
embracing the Google Drive and all that
拥抱 谷歌驱动器 和所有
kind of so you would have thought more
所以你会想得更多
people would be in Haiti know that kind
人们会 在 海地知道那种
of stuff it's incredible already knew
的东西， 这是难以置信的已经 知道
though it is pretty new and you have to
虽然它很新，你 必须这样做
remember the course that I'm in the
记住我在的课程
demographics are generally like women my
人口统计学一般都像女人一样
age and I 45 right nicely played sir I
年龄和我45很好地扮演先生 我
think the whole stem you know the with
想想你知道的 全部干
women is still growing okay you think
你认为女人还在成长
it's a gender gap perhaps are the men in
这是一个性别差距 也许是在男子
the group technology well there aren't
集团技术 还没有
any
任何
oh it's an all-female clubs yeah so yeah
哦， 这是一个全女性俱乐部，是的，所以是的
control but that's a tough thing but I I
控制，但这是一个艰难的事情，但我
do know that I've never been the
要知道我从未 成为过
smartest at Tech in the room until to be
最聪明的科技在房间里直到
fair you do hang out with a lot of geeks
你可以和很多极客一起出去玩
that's true I have access to genius it's
这是真的，我可以访问它的天才
it's tough to to gauge that when you
这很难衡量 ，当你
spend you know when your friends are
花时间告诉你的朋友
basically nerds and that's jinx not that
基本上是书呆子，那 不是那个
all your friends are know already much
所有的朋友都已经知道了
and most of your other friends Jeff
和你的大多数朋友杰夫
there are still people who buy Microsoft
还有人买微软
Office
办公室
yes there are still people who spend
是还有谁花的人
hundreds of dollars in order to get the
数百美元，以 获得
ability to do word processing in
做文字处理能力中
specialist exact that so you say like
专家确切地说，所以你说
well people are not familiar with Google
好吧人们不熟悉谷歌
Drive well no there are still there's
开得好， 没有， 还有
still that I just I think the shiaa
还是我只是认为 shiaa
transition though but I shake my head
过渡但我摇摇 头
because I'm like it's it's out there so
因为我喜欢它就在那里
blatantly obvious that now like I don't
显而易见，现在我喜欢不喜欢
know how people still do it but I'm just
知道人们如何做到 这一点，但我只是
like I think forget
就像我想的那样 忘记
up in the hole and Sasha you can you can
在洞里 和 Sasha你可以
relate to this oh well I've got all my
与此有关 哦，我已经得到了我的全部
files in docx format and I'm afraid that
docx格式的 文件， 我很害怕
if I transition I'm not gonna be able to
如果我过渡，我 将无法做到
open them but then you upload a docx
打开它们，然后你上传一个docx
file to Google Drive then boom it's
文件到谷歌驱动器 然后繁荣它
converted and it works in Drive yes so
已转换，它适用于驱动器 是的
there's really no you know when you when
你什么时候真的不知道
you factor that in it's like wow you can
你认为 它就像哇你可以
you can really make that transition now
你现在可以真正实现这一转变
yep I think that's the way the
是的， 我认为 这是的方式
technology is gone and going but I think
技术已经走了， 但我认为
Microsoft starting to feel that we're
微软开始觉得我们是
learning that this week with the changes
本周随着变化学习
in their browser you mean some to blue
在他们的浏览你的意思是一些 蓝
screen of death
死亡的屏幕
no I'm talking about edge yeah we had to
不，我说的是边缘，我们不得不这样做
talk about Microsoft edge just last week
上周谈到了 微软的优势
about how why why do they still hold on
关于为什么他们仍然坚持的原因
to that mindset we actually have that
以这种 心态，我们实际上有
discussion and the very next day they
讨论和第二天他们
announced that they're switching to
宣布 他们正在 转向
chromium yes and and this after trying
铬是和和尝试后的这个
so hard to convince people that edge is
很难说服人们有优势
better than chrome right what you're
你还有什么比铬更好
saying really is that they watch the
说真的是他们看的
show give them better advice on how to
show给他们更好的建议如何
run their business but it also shows
经营他们的业务，但它也显示
yeah that would be nice
是的那会很好
it shows that they're finally cluing in
它表明 他们终于 陷入了困境
that yes we can't pretend that this is
是的，我们不能假装这是
1985 anymore we can't pretend that this
1985年我们不能再假装 这个了
is the early 90s and we own the market
是90年代初 ，我们拥有市场
yeah that's not where we're at right
是的，那不是我们正确的地方
welcome to reality yeah so so yeah it's
欢迎来到现实，所以是的，所以是的
a transition for the users a transition
转换为用户转换
for the companies who manufacture this
对于制造这个的公司
off oh my gosh big time yep - what do
关 哦我的天哪 大的时候是的-做什么
you been up to in tech whatever you've
无论你做什么，你一直在科技
been busy I've been very busy time for
一直很忙，我一直 很忙
well oddly enough I had a meeting last
奇怪的是，我最后一次开会
Thursday okay so like the day after cat5
星期四 好吧就像cat5之后的那一天
and hanging out with some colleagues
和 一些同事一起 出去 玩
from the other side of the boardroom
从 会议室的另一边
table and they're like hey let's go out
桌子，他们就像嘿，让我们走出去
for lunch you know kind of our last
午餐 你 知道我们的最后一次
meeting before you know the holiday
在你知道假期之前见面
season so we're like okay and while
这个季节让我们感觉还好
we're out for lunch somehow the
我们出去吃午饭了
conversation ended up on cryptocurrency
谈话最终以 加密货币为主
mm-hm
嗯
and with people who know nothing about
与谁一无所知的人
anything tech they're basically like I
什么技术他们基本上像 我
have the power button on my computer and
我的电脑上有电源按钮
that's as far as it goes
这就是尽可能 去
sure so I'm talking about cryptocurrency
当然，我所说的 是加密货币
I'm talking about the blockchain and
我在谈论区块链和
they're like glazed-over look and then I
他们就像釉面看起来然后我
pulled out yeah and then when we're you
拉出来是的， 然后我们就是你
know you can mine on single board
知道你可以在单板上开采
computers and we just did an analysis
计算机，我们只是做了一个分析
analysis with the giggle score and
分析与傻笑得分和
they're like what and I was like yes
他们就像是什么，我就像是
real-time giggle score conversation he
实时傻笑得分谈话 他
made it into real life conversations
把它变成现实生活中的对话
yeah it was it was great and the best
是的，它 是伟大的，最好的
part was at the end of sup lunch sorry
部分 是在午餐结束时抱歉
the one guy is just like glazed over
一个人就像釉面一样
he's like I have no clue how you know
他就像我不知道你怎么知道的
any of that stuff I'm like well it's
任何这些 东西我都很喜欢 它
osmosis really but the other person that
反渗透真的，但其他人认为
table she's like okay this is amazing I
表她很喜欢这太棒了我
need to go buy one of those little mini
需要去购买那些小 迷你 的一个
computer things so it can make me
电脑的东西，所以它可以让 我
cryptocurrency right I'm like it's more
加密货币权利我喜欢它更多
than just that you can't just buy the
不仅仅是 你不能只买
SBC she's like okay in a world of 86 in
SBC她在86英寸的世界里也没问题
a world of Asics
Asics的世界
you're going to go with a Raspberry Pi
你会选择Raspberry Pi
zero as your crypto mining but she's
零作为你的加密采矿，但她是
like oh but if I you're gonna be
喜欢哦，但如果我要你
disappointed so if I buy one of those
失望所以如果我买 那些 之一
little like credit card computers and I
很像 信用卡电脑和我
just like let her you know do its math
就像让你知道她的数学一样
scores oh my gosh then I can make money
分数哦，我的天哪，然后我可以 赚钱
I'm like after a year you might have
我想你可能有 一年后
10,000 turtle coins
10,000乌龟硬币
quit making it a swear word sit up with
退出让它成为一个发誓的话语
me in tech is talking to people who deal
我在科技与交易的人交谈
in contracts about tech and they're just
在关于技术的合同中， 他们只是
like oh okay
好吧哦好吧
so people are interested in the tech
所以人们对科技很感兴趣
yeah it was really neat yeah it's really
是的它真的很整洁是的，它真的
neat and then I was mentioning the
整洁 ，然后我提到了
interview we had almost a year ago up
我们差不多一年前接受采访了
with blockchain and I mentioned the
与区块链，我提到了
whole idea about that the question I
关于我的问题的全部想法
raised about passports and then they
关于护照 ，然后他们
kind of got the concept of how it's all
有点理解这一切的概念
linked and we started talking about the
链接， 我们开始谈论
romaine lettuce recall of the go and I'm
长叶莴苣回忆起了 我和我
like if it's on the blockchain we'd be
就好像它是在区块链上我们会的
able to know exactly where it came from
能够准确地知道 它来自哪里
and they're going home this is a really
他们要回家了，这是真的
cool idea and then this organization
很酷的想法 然后这个组织
they also deal in logistics and I'm like
他们也处理物流， 我喜欢
you know if you guys got
你知道，如果你们有
Lock chain built into your technology
锁链 内置 于您的技术中
you'd be able to like from purchase
你可以从购买中喜欢
right through the logistics filled
通过物流填补
facility to the store shelf you'd be
设施到你 的商店货架
able to tell where all your products are
能够告诉您所有产品的位置
and how who's been involved in like oh
和谁一样参与了哦
that's interesting
这很有趣
we're gonna have to look into this for
我们将不得不考虑这个
our business I'm like there you go
我的生意我就像你去的那样
you're changing the world I don't it was
你 改变世界 我不是这样
fun
开玩笑
make it happen Jeff make it happen
实现它杰夫让它成真
single-handedly jeff has brought the
单枪匹马的杰夫带来了
blockchain to Canada not a true story it
区块链到加拿大不是一个真实的故事吧
is cool to think about how the
是冷静 地 想想如何
blockchain could prevent those kinds of
区块链可以防止这种情况
happens dances so understand when
发生舞蹈，所以明白何时
there's a product recall food in
有一个产品召回食品
particular mm-hmm they don't know where
特别是mm-hmm他们不知道在哪里
the infected food came from yeah
被感染的食物 来自 耶
generally get it down to the region yeah
通常把它 归到 该地区是的
but that's I mean it all just gets
但是这是我的意思是这一切只是 得到
dumped onto a truck and then gets dumped
倾倒在卡车上， 然后倾倒
into a factory warehouse and then gets
进入工厂仓库，然后得到
shipped out and gets warehouse and then
运出并获得仓库然后
gets distributed to the stores so maybe
可能会分发到商店
they can narrow it down to that
他们可以缩小它是
warehouse that distributed it to those
将它分发给 那些的 仓库
stores yeah but how do they know that
商店是的，但他们怎么知道
it's not also from further down the line
它不是 来自更远的线
so now okay well it may affect other
所以现在好吧它可能会影响其他人
stores even though they haven't had any
商店即使他们 没有
issues so we just have to pull all the
问题所以我们只需要全力以赴
romaine lettuce right farmers are busy
长叶莴苣对农民很忙
right
对
farmers are hurting the whole industry
农民正在伤害 整个 行业
is hurting people along those chains so
这样就伤害了那些连锁店的人
from the farm all the way to the to
从农场一直到 到
table yeah yeah I mean not to sound too
表是啊是啊我的意思是不发声
cliche but all the way up to the store
陈词滥调，但一直到商店
the entire supply chain is affected by
整个供应链受到影响
those types of recalls yeah not only
那些类型的召回不仅是的
that but the amount of waste think about
但浪费的数量却在想
it okay so here's what I think I think
它好了，这里就是我 想 我想
if blockchain could be used that I bet
如果可以使用区块链， 我打赌
you we would find that a contamination
你我们会发现污染
like that probably isn't it entirely
这可能不是完全的
field wide I bet you if you were right
场 宽 我敢打赌你，如果你是对的
so it's only an apportion probably so
所以这可能只是一个分配
even the waste from the actual firm that
甚至是来自实际公司的废物
may be yeah yeah like everything could
可能是的，是的，就像一切都可以
save money right along the line but it's
沿着这条线省钱但是就是 这样
about investing in the technology to
关于 技术投资，以
make it happen though and
让它成为现实
I mean even just in the vegetable
我的意思是即使 只是在蔬菜中
industry to get that in one probably
行业可能在一个人
it's a good example yeah exactly
这是一个很好的 例子，是的
but I mean that would be like massive
但我的意思是，这将是巨大的
infrastructure right and and mind shift
基础设施权利和 思想转变
to make it happen but to think of all
让它成为现实，但 想到 所有
the positivity that could come as a
可能来自的积极性
result of it cuz I love it so think
它的结果 因为我爱它 所以想
about it like say at the farm where
关于它就像在农场说的那样
romaine lettuce is being farmed sorry
长叶莴苣正在养殖抱歉
groan do you call it drumming hecht
呻吟你叫它打鼓hecht
it'll be like it'll be cultivated there
它会像在那里种植一样
you go that sounds about right
你听起来是 对的
my very limited knowledge of farming so
我对农业的知识非常有限
imagine that there's an individual with
想象一下有个人
some kind of ailment that they have now
他们现在 有某种疾病
introduced into that supply chain I've
介绍了我的供应链
learned about set ailment okay so now
现在就了解到设置疾病好了
this supply so no ten crates of romaine
这个供应所以没有十箱的长叶莴苣
lettuce now has gone out to the supply
生菜现在上场 供应
chain right because of those ten crates
因为 那十个板条箱而正确连锁
of lettuce that are contaminated now
现在 被 污染 的生菜
somebody gets sick yeah and they have to
有人生病是的，他们必须
now pull all of the romaine lettuce from
现在从中拉出所有的生菜
the entire country wrong all the lettuce
整个国家错了所有的 生菜
in the entire country think about if the
在整个国家想想 如果
block chain can now say oh no this was
块链现在可以说哦不， 这是
just that one worker mm-hmm and these
只有那个工人mm-hmm和这些
ten crates and we can pull those ten
十箱，我们可以拉十个
crates that's all yep think about the
所有人都在考虑这个问题
amount of food that now is being
现在 的 食物 量
recalled that can now let's just put
回想一下， 现在可以放手吧
that into perspective what if we could
如果我们能做到这一点的话
take that food that was recalled and and
把那些被召回的食物和
give that to a third world or two hungry
把它交给第三个世界或两个饥饿的人
people right and just imagine how much
人们 正确，想象多少
good food that is that is basically just
良好的食物，这是 基本上只是
being expired because they can't do
因为无法做到 而 过期
anything with it cuz they don't know
任何与它有关的 因为他们不知道
where the contamination took place this
发生污染的地方
using the block chain is a great way
使用区块链是一个很好的方法
technology can help to save the world
技术可以帮助拯救世界
really absolutely so all right we're not
真的绝对 如此， 我们不是
here to talk about food but the
这里谈谈食物但是
blockchain I'll talk about exactly yeah
blockchain我将谈论 究竟 是啊
and we're all learning at the same time
而 我们都在学习的同时，
we're all learning together because this
我们都在一起学习，因为这个
is an evolving technology and it's
是一种不断发展的技术，它是
something that we're seeing with
我们正在 与 看到的东西
companies like Walmart and Intel
沃尔玛和英特尔等公司
investing in the technology to make this
投资技术来实现这一目标
happen and if Walmart can bring that in
发生了，如果沃尔玛可以把它带进来
then all of a sudden the value of the
然后突然之间的价值了
blockchain also goes up I'm going to
区块链也会上升我要去
start to see a value increase in the
开始看到价值增加了
cryptocurrency market as well because
加密货币市场也是如此
it's all part of the same kind of
它都属于同一类型
infrastructure of that blockchain so so
该区块链的基础设施如此
it's interesting how everything kind of
这是怎么样的有趣的一切
plays into one another in this very
玩 到彼此在 这个
strange evolving technological world
奇怪的进化技术世界
that we live in so in a completely
我们生活在一个完全
self-serving thought process last week
上周自私的思想过程
we mentioned the whole Microsoft issue
我们提到了整个微软的问题
an edge and suddenly the next day they
一个边缘， 第二天突然间他们
switch and then you know say a year and
切换，然后你知道说一年和
a half or now suddenly we see some
一半或现在我们突然看到一些
blockchain and some produce could we say
我们可以说区块链和一些 产品
it you know yeah sure a cat5 we can't
它你知道是的， 我们 确定 不能
because it was a news story and Sasha
因为这是一个新闻故事和 Sasha
unveiled it well we could just forget
很好地揭开它我们可以忘记
about that part we're changing the world
关于 那部分我们正在改变这个世界
you heard it here you heard it here so
你在这听说过， 你在这里听到了
give us a thumbs up give this a try when
给我们竖起大拇指试试这个 时
you have all that kind of stuff you know
你把所有的那种东西 ，你知道
how that works
它是如何工作
yeah technology wise for me this week
是的， 本周对我来说技术明智
because I know that was the question the
因为我知道那是个问题
year oh yes yeah here's the thing you
一年哦是的是的，这就是你的事
you're everything tech like I'm your
你是一切技术，就像我是你的
part cyborg you're all text I'm kinda
部分机器人你是所有文本我有点
I've got my hands in so many different
我有很多不同的手
things I'm loving the single board
事我喜欢单板
computers I'm loving that portable like
电脑我很喜欢便携式电脑
very micro and learning and and trying
非常微观，学习和尝试
to become a maker and learning to solder
成为制造商并学习焊接
and things like that being able to
这样的事情能够
program a single board computer even an
编程 单板计算机甚至是
Arduino to do some cool stuff it's a lot
Arduino做了很多很酷的事情
of fun for me sure
对我来说很有趣
but I'm stepping back you know christmas
但我退后一步，你知道圣诞节
is coming okay there's not a lot of time
即将到来 ，没有太多时间
to mess around with that kind of thing
与 这种事情浪费时间
mm-hmm
毫米-HMM
so tonight we're looking at the smart
所以今晚我们正在考虑聪明
home devices that you can purchase that
您可以购买的家用设备
are ready to rock out the door mm-hmm
准备好摇 出门 - 嗯
we're gonna do things like okay google
我们要做好像谷歌这样的事情
turn on the light we're gonna say Alexa
打开灯我们会说Alexa
turn off the light and that is cool to
关灯，这 很酷
me
我
we're gonna learn all about it tonight
我们今晚要学习所有 这些
on category five technology TV we got to
在 五级技术的电视，我们得
take a quick break they'll stick around
快点休息，他们会坚持下去
we'll be right back
我们马上回来
[Music]
[音乐]
whether you shop on ThinkGeek gearbest
你是否购买ThinkGeek gearbest
PNH photo/video ebay or amazon or even
PNH照片/视频易趣或亚马逊甚至
if you want a free trial of audible
如果你想要免费试听听觉
you'll find the best deals and support
你会找到最好的交易和支持
the shows we produce by simply visiting
我们通过简单 访问 制作的节目
the shopping sites you already frequent
你经常去的购物网站
by using the links on our website visit
通过使用我们网站上的链接 访问
category 5 TV slash partners for the
5类 电视斜线合作伙伴
full and ever-growing list and help us
完整且不断增长的清单 并帮助我们
create more free content like this show
创建更多像这个 节目的 免费内容
thank you for shopping with our partners
感谢您与我们的合作伙伴一起购物
and thank you for watching all right
感谢您的收看 没事
welcome back we're gonna get straight
欢迎回来我们会 挺直的
into it we've got an amazon echo dot
进入它 我们有一个亚马逊回声 点
third-generation we've got a Google home
第三代 我们有一个谷歌的家
mini
微型
they're about the same price okay as you
他们是差不多的价格 没关系， 你
can see they're roughly let's see if I
我们可以看到他们大致让我们看看
can get in here if I can click the right
如果我可以点击右边，可以进入这里
buttons they're roughly the same form
按钮它们的形状 大致 相同
factor so they look about the same about
因素 ，使他们看起来差不多 的约
the same color shoe yeah yeah they're
相同颜色的鞋子是啊是的他们是
and stylistically they're pretty similar
在风格上他们非常相似
there are some differences before we get
在 我们得到 之前 有一些 差异
into the review before we start actually
在 我们实际开始 之前进入审查
testing these devices which are smart
测试这些智能设备
home devices if you're not familiar with
家庭设备，如果你不熟悉
them we're gonna be showing you how they
他们我们会 告诉 你 他们 是 怎么回事
work in just a couple of moments time I
工作在短短 片刻时间，我的
actually filmed as I unboxed these so
实际上我拍摄的是这样的
let's get in there and let's take a look
让我们进去， 让我们来看看
at the boxes that's what they look like
在他们看起来像什么的盒子
and okay I've got the Google home many
好吧我有很多Google 家
I'm gonna set aside and let's get into
我会 抛开 ，让我们进入
the box for the echo dot this is the
回声点 的 方框 就是这个
third-generation as I mentioned there so
正如我在那里提到的第三代
this is the current one in 2018 at the
这是 2018年 的 当前版本
end of the year so this is what you're
今年年底所以这就是你的意思
gonna be picking up if you if you get
会有所回升 ，如果你，如果你得到
one of these for for a Christmas gift or
对于圣诞礼物 ，这些 对一个或
something like that nicely packaged you
这样的东西很好地打包你
can see that a lot of detail has gone
可以看到很多细节已经消失
into the packaging and it's not loose
进入包装并且没有松动
within that box it's really really it's
在那个盒子里，真的很棒
it's well form to the box
这是很好的 形式 向箱
looking at this first of all the one
看着这首先是一个
thing that I noticed is that there are a
我注意到的事情是有一个
lot of buttons on top you got the four
你 上面 有很多按钮
buttons here we don't have that at least
这里的按钮我们 至少 没有 这个
not visible on the on the Google device
在Google设备上看不到
spinning around I've got power here and
在我周围 旋转 我有 力量
I've also got interestingly enough what
我也有趣得到了什么
looks like a headphone jack or an audio
看起来像耳机插孔或音频
output so I can actually connect this to
输出所以我可以实际连接到
a bigger speaker system if I want and
如果我想要和更大的扬声器系统
I've also got the ability to use
我也得到了 使用 的能力
headphones with it so I have tested this
耳机，所以我 测试了这个
as a podcast broadcasting tool so I
作为一个播客广播工具，所以我
plugged my headphones in and listen to a
把我的耳机塞进去听一听
podcast from the echo dot and it works
来自回声点的播客， 它的工作原理
just fine
正好
it's got the basic manuals as you'd
它有基本手册， 你会
imagine but you notice that with these
想象但你会注意到 这些
devices they're very they're very
设备他们非常 非常
limited as far as their manuals go
至于他们的手册去限制
because there's no a lot to learn
因为没有太多要学的东西
they're self-explanatory presumably and
他们是不言自明的推测 和
we've got a power brick there which is a
我们在那里有一块电源砖
barrel connector into the Amazon echo
桶连接器进入亚马逊回声
dot nice okay so let's let's pull out
点好不好让我们退出吧
the Google device so this is that's the
Google设备就是这样的
Amazon echo dot third gen and I've also
亚马逊回声点 第三 代 ， 我也是
got the Google home Mini which is again
得到了谷歌 家用迷你 再次
current as Alexa giving us a hard time
目前，Alexa让我们很难过
Alexa cancel the Google home mini is
Alexa的取消谷歌的家 是 小
this is what is current at the end of
这就是目前的结果
2018 as well so these were both ordered
2018年以及这些都是订购的
the same day and there it is so similar
同一天，它是如此相似
kind of form factor but you notice now
一种 外形，但你现在注意到了
this one the speaker is on the top it's
这一个扬声器位于顶部
not wrapped around as you see with the
如你所见，没有缠绕
Amazon echo dot three input wise there's
亚马逊回声点 三输入明智
literally nothing there's no buttons
几乎没有什么没有按钮
that you can feel now I have discovered
你现在觉得我已经发现了
that there are volume buttons on the
上有 音量按钮
side but they're basically like a touch
一边， 但他们基本上就像一个触摸
sensor then we've got the power input
传感器， 然后我们有电源输入
which is USB mini and we've got a switch
这是 USB mini ，我们有一个开关
to turn on and off its ability to listen
打开和关闭它的 听力
to me so I always thought when I saw
对我来说，所以当我看到的时候我一直在想
this ok well this one's got the physical
这很好，这个人有物理
switch doesn't look like really anything
开关看起来不像 什么
else but because it has a physical
否则，因为它有一个物理
switch I thought that's going to be the
开关我以为那将是
one because I can I can mute it I can
一个，因为我可以，我可以将其静音
make it so it it's not a privacy concern
这样做不是隐私问题
we talked about that in a few moments
我们在片刻谈到了这一点
again we've got very basic manuals
我们再次获得了非常基本的手册
because presumably they're gonna talk
因为大概他们 会说话
back to you and they're gonna teach you
回到你身边，他们会教你
how to set them up and they're gonna
如何设置 他们，他们会
walk you through the steps pretty simply
简单地指导 您完成 各个步骤
we are at that point in technology which
我们正处在技术 点 ，这
I love pretty cool stuff
我喜欢很酷的 东西
and then we've got a USB see can or a
然后我们有一个USB 看到 罐头或一个
USB micro USB yeah micro connector and
USB micro USB 是的 微型连接器和
it's got its own power there perfect
它有完美的自己的力量
other than that anything else in the box
除了盒子里的任何其他东西
that is everything in the box so nice
这就是盒子里的一切都很好
and simple nice and sleek that's all it
这简直美好而时尚
comes with folks so those are the two
有人， 所以 那些是两个
devices on your left is the the Google
左侧的设备是Google
home mini and on the right is the Amazon
家用迷你 ，在右边是亚马逊
echo dot and it's third-generation there
echo dot和它的第三代
you have it alright so let's let's
你没事，所以让我们来吧
actually get a look at these live in
实际上看看这些活着
real time on the on the desk here there
在这里的桌子上的实时
they are
他们是
so I mentioned with the Google mini it
所以我提到谷歌mini它
has a physical tactile switch which will
有一个物理触觉开关， 将
actually turn off the microphone and if
实际上关闭话筒 ，如果
I flip that mice off it'll actually tell
我把那些 老鼠 翻了 下来，实际上 我 会说
me that the mic is off and it's gone red
我， 麦克风关闭 ，它变红了
and now it's not able to hear me so if I
如果我，现在它无法听到我的声音
say ok Google ok Google
说好的谷歌确定谷歌
it doesn't respond and before I start
在我开始之前它没有回应
doing this and I apologize because I ok
这样做 ，我道歉，因为我没事
mic is on please if you use these
如果 您使用这些麦克风请 打开
devices at home mute them right now ok
在家里的设备 ，现在 确定 他们静音
because we are going to be going through
因为我们要 经历
this demonstration we're going to be
这个示范我们将会 是
calling on these devices I don't want to
呼吁这些设备，我不想
be setting off your devices I know and I
被掀起你的 设备 我知道，我
know that's gonna happen it actually
知道实际上它会发生
happened just during the break there
发生在休息期间
somebody mentioned that that we turned
有人提到我们转过身来
off their lights and I apologize but
关灯 ，我道歉 但是
that's gonna happen also an important
那也会发生重要的事情
note that we have not subscribed to any
请注意，我们尚未订阅 任何 订阅
of their extra services ok Amazon music
他们的额外服务确定 亚马逊音乐
Google Music we have not subscribed to
我们尚未订阅的Google音乐
those things because I want to feel what
那些东西，因为我想要感受到什么
it's like as a new user out of the box
它就像一个 开箱 即用的新用户
what is it like to actually use this
是 什么样实际使用
device so we may get rejected by some of
设备， 所以我们可能会被一些人拒绝
the requests that we make because we
因为我们所做的要求
don't have those subscriptions but it's
没有那些订阅，但它是
anytime I want to show you what you're
任何时候我想告诉你你是什么
going to get out of the box without
要得到 开箱无
having to pay extra advance subscription
必须支付额外的预订
fees now that said we do have an Amazon
现在说我们有亚马逊的费用
account okay obviously I use Amazon and
帐号好吧显然我使用亚马逊和
with that I do have Prime right yeah I
我确实有Prime， 是的，是的
also have G suite account because I use
也有G套房帐户，因为我使用
Gmail as my email provider yeah so
Gmail作为我的 电子邮件提供商是的
between the two providers those are the
两个提供商之间的那些
services that I do pay for each month
服务， 我不支付每月
mm-hmm and that's it so we haven't
mm-hmm就是这样我们没有
subscribe to anything extra if you get
如果 你得到，请 订阅任何 额外的 东西
the Google based device and you don't
基于谷歌的设备而你却没有
have a G suite does that impact the
有一个G套件确实影响了
services you can get from the device I
你可以从我的设备获得的服务
honestly I don't know Jeff I don't think
老实说，我不知道杰夫，我不认为
that there's anything really tapped into
有任何真正的东西
it other than that it taps into my gmail
它除了它点击 我的Gmail
and everything like that if I want to
如果我愿意，那就是那样的
give it permission to do so and but but
允许这样做但是但是
this is really just I want to be
这 真的只是我想 成为的
transparent with the viewers so that you
透明 与 观众，以便你
understand what what I have what I've
明白我拥有什么
done and I and and some people will do a
完成，我和一些人会做一个
review of these devices and they'll set
审查这些设备 ，他们将设置
up all the accounts and they'll pay for
把所有的账户， 他们会支付
the extra additionals and they'll show
额外的额外和他们将显示
you all the wonderful features I don't
你不是我所有的精彩功能
want to do that this is a box this is if
想要这样做这是一个 盒子，这是如果
you bought this for mom or dad what are
你为妈妈或爸爸买了这个是什么
they going to experience they're not
他们会 去体验他们不是
gonna want to set up a subscription base
会 想建立 一个用户群
and maybe they will but out of the box
也许他们会开箱即用
what's the experience gonna be like
什么是经验会是什么样的
that's where this review is that okay
那个评论就是 好的
out of the box and user experience in
开箱和用户体验
addition to that I should mention that
除此之外，我应该提到这一点
we are partnered with Amazon so while
我们与亚马逊合作
I'd love you to buy the Amazon device
我爱你买亚马逊设备
because we do get a cut if you use our
因为如果你使用我们的话，我们会得到削减
link I'm just full disclosure right the
链接我只是完全披露 了
the review itself is completely unbiased
审查本身完全没有偏见
I want you to be able to see both
我希望你能够看到两者
devices we're gonna we're gonna ask them
设备，我们要问他们
the same questions we're gonna allow
同样的问题，我们将允许
them to react and I want you to be able
他们要做出反应，我希望你能够 做到
to make a decision based on your own use
根据 自己的用途 做出 决定
what's going to work best for you so so
这是怎么回事到 最适合你，所以
yes we are partnered with Amazon I'd
是的，我们与亚马逊合作我
love you to buy them we're not partnered
爱你买他们我们没有合作
with Google but but you'll notice
与谷歌，但你会注意到
through the course of this review that
通过这次审查的 过程
we're not allowing that to skew our our
我们不允许这 会扭曲我们的
judgments at all of the devices again
再次 判断所有设备
please turn off the microphones on your
请关掉你的麦克风
devices so that we don't set them off if
设备， 以便我们不设置它们
you've got a phone that uses the Google
你有一部使用谷歌的手机
assistant make sure you turn that off
助理确保你把它关掉
just for the moment and because we don't
只是 暂时而且因为我们没有
want to be ordering things for you
想为你订购东西
yep alright so back into it let's get in
好吧，好吧回到 它让我们进去
here okay so we've got a tactile switch
这没关系所以我们有一个 触觉开关
on the Google home Mini and and I
在谷歌家迷你和我
thought that the Amazon echo dot didn't
以为亚马逊回声点没有
have such a thing because it doesn't
有这样的事情，因为它没有
really boast of it and this really shows
真的吹嘘它，这 真的显示
it off like that's the only tactile
就像那是唯一的触觉
thing that it has the only thing that
它有 唯一的东西
you see on the Google home is a switch
你在Google家中看到的是一个开关
to turn off its ability to listen to you
关闭它 听 你 的 能力
so I thought in my naivety that well
所以 我在 天真认为 很好
that's the device for me because we want
这是我的设备因为我们想要的
to be able to turn off that because
能够关闭那个因为
we're concerned about security and
我们担心安全问题
privacy we want to be able to turn that
隐私，我们希望能够 扭转这一局面
off yes well what I didn't realize is
关闭 是很好的是我不知道的是
that the Amazon echo dot also has this
， 亚马逊 回声点也 有这
so if I push that button there oh now
所以，如果我按那个按钮 那里 现在哦
the speaker is off so Alexa Alexa
扬声器是关闭所以Alexa Alexa
completely unresponsive it's not
完全没有反应但事实并非如此
listening to me right now the microphone
现在听我的 麦克风
is in fact muted so if I unmute that
实际上是静音的， 所以如果我取消静音
Alexa and now it's waiting for my
Alexa 现在正在等 我的
command
命令
Alexa cancel all right see Alexa cancel
Alexa取消可以看到Alexa取消
I think I just called home alright so a
我想我刚 回家 就好 了
couple of things that I've learned so
我学到的 几件事情
I've had this since Sunday so in three
自从星期天以来，我已经有三个
days now since I've had these two
现在日 以来，我有这两个
devices and I've given them both a fair
设备，我给他们两个公平
chance and given them a fair test
机会，给他们一个公平的考验
against one another and the one thing
相互对立，一件事
that I'll say for you parents of young
我会 说你 父母的年轻
children I thought that these switches
孩子我以为 这些开关
to turn off the microphone were for
关闭麦克风是为了
privacy I honestly thought that I
隐私我老实以为我
thought because my wife and I have
想，因为我的妻子 和我
private conversations we talked about
我们谈到的私人谈话
the finances and whatever else and our
财务和其他任何和我们的
romantic things and we don't want Google
浪漫的事情，我们不希望谷歌
listening we don't want Amazon listening
听我们不希望亚马逊听
so that's what those switches are for
这就是那些开关的用途
what I found out is that those switches
我发现的是那些开关
are in fact so that when you're
事实上 ，这样 当你
listening to Christmas music and your
听圣诞音乐和你的
kids come in and they tell Alexa to fart
孩子们进来， 他们告诉Alexa放屁
alexa fart looks the ball over that's
亚历山大 屁看着那个球
what those switches are for right
那些开关是 对的
i had in in one evening our first
我在一个晚上进入了我们的第一个
evening of having it i had Christmas
我有圣诞节的晚上
music playing for the kids oh yeah and
为孩子们演奏的音乐 哦耶和华
they set it up so that the Amazon echo
他们设置它以便 亚马逊回响
dot would send them a reminder every 15
dot会每隔15分发一次提醒
minutes to fart music playing and then
分钟放屁 音乐 然后播放
turn the microphone off sure can oh that
关闭麦克风肯定可以哦
is genius that's not if you can get out
是天才， 如果你能脱身就 不是
with both devices okay okay so we're
两个设备都还可以，所以我们
gonna give these two a fair shot so
要给这两个人一个公平的机会
we've got Alexa tell me a joke Jimmy
我们有Alexa告诉我一个笑话Jimmy
Fallon take it away
法伦把它拿走了
what is it horses favorite band Stalin
什么是马 最喜欢的乐队 斯大林
knows okay alright well okay Google tell
知道 好吧好吧 好吧 谷歌告诉
me a joke why is Peter Pan always flying
我开玩笑为什么彼得潘总是飞
because he can never Neverland
因为他永远不会梦幻般的
huh why is Peter Pan always flying
为什么小飞侠总是飞
because he'd never Neverland we got it
因为他从来没有Neverland我们得到它
twice alright so they both told me a
两次都好，所以他们都告诉我了
joke
玩笑
neither was over-the-top no ok Google
既不是过度的顶部 没有 确定 谷歌
fart the kids love oh ok ok Google
屁孩子们爱哦， 好吧 好吧谷歌
didn't do it maybe it was silent but
不这样做也许是沉默但是
violent now I do that because my cue
暴力现在我这样做是因为我的暗示
well that's a disappointment to record a
记录一个 令人失望的事情
problem you can send feedback like to
你可以发送反馈的问题
report that my device doesn't fart it
报告我的设备没有放屁
doesn't but the kids for some reason
由于某种原因 ，孩子们不会这样做
that's the first thing that they
这是他们的第一件事
experimented with now my wife and I were
现在我和我的妻子进行了实验
having a discussion in the kitchen where
在 厨房里 讨论
and I made you'll you'll maybe
我告诉你，也许你
appreciate this so I used coconut milk
欣赏这一点，所以我用椰奶
to make a not a creme brle custard ok
做 一个不是奶油brûlée乳蛋糕 好
and said oh we should make creme brulee
并说哦， 我们应该做焦糖布丁
right now that I've made a vegan
现在我已经做了素食主义者
alternative to coconut milk it was with
椰子奶的替代品
with cornstarch instead of egg
用玉米淀粉代替鸡蛋
and I pulled it off it actually was
我把它关闭它实际上 是
really really good excellent my wife
真是太棒了我老婆
said to me well is that all creme brulee
对我说好的是所有焦糖布丁
is is custard mm-hmm and I said Alexa is
是什么乳蛋糕mm-hmm，我说Alexa是
creme brulee made of custard here's
奶油布丁是由乳蛋糕制成的
something I found on Wikipedia creme
这是我在维基百科上找到奶油
brulee also known as burn cream or
布丁也被称为烧伤膏或
Trinity cream is a dessert consisting of
Trinity 奶油是一种甜点
a rich custard base topped with a
一个富含乳蛋糕的基地，上面有一个
texturally contrasting layer of hardened
质地对比的硬化层
caramelized sugar ok google' is creme
焦糖糖好谷歌'是奶油
brulee made of custard on the website
布鲁尔在网站上用蛋奶制作
Vespa seats calm
大黄蜂座位平静
they say creme brulee the simple and
他们说creme brulee 简单而且
elegant custard creme brulee is a
优雅的奶油焦糖布丁是一个
classic French dessert consisting of a
经典的法国甜点组成的
custard topped with caramelized sugar
乳蛋糕配上焦糖
very nice finish search results yes
非常好的 完成搜索结果 是的
basic yeah same same result different
基本是啊同样的结果不同
verbage okay but they both worked they
verbage 不错，但他们都工作 ，他们
both answered my question which is
两个都回答了我的问题
important to me I want to be able to ask
对我来说很重要，我希望 能够 提出
questions and that's a part of the idea
问题，这 是这个想法 的一部分
behind having an assistant now if you
现在 背后 有 一个助手 ，如果你
use either of these on your phone what I
在 我的手机 上使用其中任何一个
have noticed is that these are way
注意到这些都是这样的
faster the response time is
响应时间越快
instantaneous is that because it's using
瞬间是 因为 它正在使用
your cell phone data well on my phone
你 的手机数据好于我的手机
it's slow on my phone if I ask a
如果我问的话，我的手机 很慢
question if I ask these same questions
如果我问这些相同的 问题 我会有 疑问
they're delayed in order to give me that
为了给我这个，他们被推迟了
answer with either of these devices
回答这些设备中的任何一个
especially honestly the Google seems to
特别老实说谷歌似乎
be really zippy they are very quick to
真的很活泼 他们很快
answer the question so when I ask a
当我问一个问题时回答这个问题
question is instantly there it knows the
问题是它立刻就知道了
answer it's not waiting my phone on the
回答它不是在等我的手机
other hand using the same like Google
另一方面像谷歌一样使用它
assistant for example it seems to have a
助理，例如它似乎有一个
bit of a delay okay one of the so now
有点延迟好吧 现在就这样了
okay well what use is that that's cool
好吧，那很酷的是什么用途
that's really neat and everything but we
除了我们之外，这真的很整洁
want to be able to do things like okay
希望能够做这样的事情 好吗
google turn on the light turning the
谷歌打开灯 转动
light on and that to me starts to take
点亮，我开始采取
this into the next level so okay Google
这进入下一个 级别，所以 谷歌好
Google I know and I do find that Ansel
谷歌我知道，我确实找到了安塞尔
I'll need your permission okay go to me
我需要 你的许可 好的，请转到我这里
and cancel it gets confused sometimes if
并取消它有时会混淆如果
you start talking and you've already
你开始说话了， 你已经说过了
said the key word and I do find okay
说关键词，我确实找到了
Google is a bit of a tongue twister
谷歌有点绕口令
just write again close the light I turn
再写一下， 关上我转过的灯
off the light sorry I'm not sure how to
光明对不起 我不知道该怎么做
help with that that's my fault not yours
帮助 那是我的 错不是你的
okay Google turn off the light you got
好吧 谷歌 关闭了你的光
it
它
turning off the light do you find that a
关灯， 你发现了吗？
tongue-twister a little bit mm-hmm no no
绕口令 有点mm-hmm不行
okay I kind of do
好吧， 我 有点 喜欢
Alexa turn on the light okay not a
Alexa 打开灯好吧不是
tongue-twister at all I don't get
绕口令我根本不知道
tongue-tied on that do you wanna try
舌头绑在那你想尝试
I have a question act okay can you turn
我有一个问题的行为没关系 ，你可以打开
down the volume of the response because
降低响应量 因为
okay the time I would want to turn off
好吧，我想要关闭的 时间
the light is if I was sleepy so Alexa
光是如果我困了所以Alexa
volume 1 Alexa turn off the light
第 1 卷 Alexa 关灯
beautiful Thanks Alexa volume 7 okay
非常感谢Alexa第7卷好吧
Google volume 7 Alexa turn on the light
Google第7卷Alexa开灯了
okay okay Google
还好 还好 谷歌
turn off the light you got it turning
关掉它转动的灯
off the light now you notice that we
关了灯 ，现在 你注意到我们
have a light bulb there and it's just
那里有一个灯泡而且只是
connected to a smart device here which
连接到这里的智能设备
is just a power bar so this is a Wi-Fi
只是一个电源栏， 所以这是一个Wi-Fi
connected power bar which cost me no
连接电源吧，我不花钱
more than normal power bar and yet it
超过正常的电源杆，但它
has connectivity to these devices
与这些设备连接
through Wireless so I can have that
通过无线，所以我可以有
anywhere and all four of those power
任何地方和所有四个权力
outlets plus the USB can be controlled
可以控制插座和USB
by voice via either of these devices and
通过这些设备之一的语音和
that's why I can say okay Google turn on
这就是为什么我可以说 谷歌好 了
the light okay turning on the light but
光还可以打开灯 ， 但是
then I can also say Alexa turn off the
然后我也可以说Alexa 关闭了
light okay so they play nicely together
光还好，所以他们一起玩得很好
they interact together they do what I
他们一起互动他们做我的事
don't like though is that with the
不喜欢虽然是这样 的
Google device it keeps repeating what
谷歌设备不断重复什么
I've told it to do I that's why I like
我告诉它我这就是我喜欢的原因
sometimes in the verbage yeah I've
有时在废话是的我
sensed that sometimes that's why I like
感觉到有时这就是我喜欢的原因
the okay I don't want to give our
好吧 我不想给我们
opinion too much that's my I want you to
意见太多，这是我想要你的
make your opinion so but keep that in
让您的意见左右，但记住这
mind and listen for that I think that's
记住并倾听 我的想法
fair
公平
now we can't play like music here on the
现在我们不能在这里播放音乐了
review because then we're gonna be
审查， 因为那样我们会
monetize on YouTube but I do want to
在YouTube上获利， 但我确实想要
show you how easy it is to request
向您展示请求是多么容易
certain genres of music so here it is
某些类型的音乐，所以在这里
it's
它的
December 11th when we're shooting this
12月11日我们拍摄的时候
so I would say okay google play some
所以我会说好吧谷歌玩一些
Christmas music alright here's a Google
圣诞音乐好吧， 这是谷歌
Play Music station called smooth R&amp;B
播放音乐电台称为平滑的R＆B
Christmas okay okay so it works and I
圣诞节还 可以， 所以它和我一起工作
can say okay google skip this song
可以说 好吧 谷歌跳过这首歌
sounds okay what singer is this this has
听起来不错， 这是什么歌手
real love this Christmas by Kenny
肯尼真的很喜欢这个圣诞节
Lattimore
拉铁摩尔
okay Google stop the music which is
没关系 谷歌停止音乐 是
pretty cool when you're listening to
你在听的时候很酷
music and you can just ask it what Lance
音乐，你可以问它 兰斯
is playing because quite often on the
正在玩，因为经常在
regular radio you don't necessarily
定期收音机你 不一定
catch who it is yeah Alexa played me
抓住谁是 Alexa Alexa扮演我
some Christmas music the station holiday
一些圣诞音乐站的假期
favorites on Amazon music you notice how
您注意到亚马逊音乐的最爱
I can just use regular verbage yeah yeah
我可以只 使用常规verbage呀呀
Alexa skip this song and I like that but
Alexa 跳过这首歌我很喜欢
I can just talk to these devices as if
我可以 像 对待 这些 设备 一样
they're in the room and just doing my
他们在房间里，只是做我的
bidding
投标
Alexa stop the music and Alexa will do
Alexa停止音乐 ，Alexa会这样做
it will do the same response I should
我会做同样的回应
say Alexa play me some Christmas music
说Alexa 给我一些圣诞音乐
Alexa play some Christmas music the
Alexa演奏了一些圣诞音乐
station holiday favorites on Amazon
亚马逊的车站假日收藏
music I want this to be fair one two one
音乐 我希望这 是公平的 两个一个
Alexa what singer is this this is
Alexa这是什么歌手
Michael Buble okay Alexa what CD is this
Michael Buble 好的Alexa CD是什么
from Cedric Donald Atkins was a
来自塞德里克唐纳德阿特金斯是一个
researcher for the United States
研究员为美国
Department of Agriculture completely off
农业部完全 关闭
that answer your question no but to be
回答你的 问题， 但不是
fair I didn't ask that question of the
公平的我没有问过这个问题
okay one all right Alexa cancel all
没关系 Alexa 全部取消
right so it's able to tell me who the
对，所以它能告诉我是谁
singer is and once I get used to the
歌手是，一旦我习惯了
commands of each in there a little bit
在 有一点点 的 每个命令
each one is a little bit different yes
每个人都有点不同
but that does it's able to look it up
但是它能够查找它
for me really really quickly again very
对我来说真的非常快
very quick we're able to skip music on
很快我们就可以跳过音乐了
both devices
两种设备
fantastic now we can get in to some
太棒了， 现在我们可以进入一些
royalty-free music and this is where I
免版税音乐，这就是 我的地方
want to talk about the quality of the
想谈谈质量 问题
speakers okay
扬声器没关系
so I have personally found and again we
所以我亲自找到了我们
don't want to get into personal my
不要想 进入我的个人
opinion too much but I do want to tell
意见太多但我确实想告诉
you through the experience over the past
通过 过去 的 经验
couple of days and this has been
几天 ，这已经 过去了
reiterated by other staff in the office
办公室其他工作人员重申
because I've had both of these devices
因为我有这两种 设备 的
playing Christmas music in my office and
在我的办公室里演奏圣诞音乐
this is and I did not prompt them they
这是，我没有提示他们
came to me and said they prefer the
来到我 面前 说 他们更喜欢这个
Alexa device over pardon me a cancel
Alexa的设备在 原谅我 取消
they prefer the Amazon echo dot over the
他们更喜欢亚马逊的回声点
Google home mini really the Google home
谷歌家迷你 真的 是谷歌的家
mini sounds like a good Bluetooth
迷你听起来像一个很好的蓝牙
speaker right like what you would expect
说话者就像你期望的那样
from a little Bluetooth speaker right
从一个蓝牙小音箱右侧
the Amazon echo dot third gen sounds
亚马逊回声点 第三代 声音
like a really good full speaker and and
就像一个非常好的演讲者和
it's pretty much the same form factor
这几乎是 相同的 外形尺寸
but it does have a much fuller sound and
但 它确实有更丰满的声音 和
I hope that we can demonstrate that
我希望我们可以证明这一点
tonight certainly these two will be able
今晚肯定这两项就能
to give their judgement and I have a
给出他们的判断 ，我有一个
recorder in front here so what you're
记录器在这里前面所以你是什么
going to hear is going to be from right
听到的将是正确的
in front here from a good quality zoom
在这里从 优质的变焦
h4n and it should be able to pick it up
h4n 它应该能够 拿起它
a little bit anyway so that you can get
一点点 无论如何，这样你可以得到
a bit of a judgement so okay google play
有点判断，所以 好吧谷歌玩
the fat rat that artist is only
艺术家的肥胖老鼠
available for google play music
可用于谷歌播放音乐
subscribers see that but try this google
订阅者看到，但试试这个谷歌
play music the fat rat station okay
播放音乐胖鼠站 好吧
okay Google what song is this this is
好吧谷歌 什么 歌是这样的 ，这是
time lapse by the fat track royalty-free
时间流逝的 胖 赛道免版税
[Music]
[音乐]
set the volume to five that's kind of
音量设置为5 这是一种
the impression that I got is it's good
我得到的印象是 好的
it's okay it's like a Bluetooth speaker
没关系，就像 蓝牙音箱一样
you're right it sounds like something
你是对的听起来 像是什么
you pick up for 20 bucks yeah it's just
你拿起20块钱， 是的，它只是
like and and to be fair they're not
喜欢和公平他们 不是
expensive both these devices right price
这两种设备价格合理
like similarly to one another we're not
我们不喜欢彼此相似
gonna talk about pricing but if they're
谈谈 定价， 但如果他们是
not an expensive device and it does work
不是一个昂贵的设备，它确实有效
as a Bluetooth speaker but that's all it
作为蓝牙音箱，但就是这样
sounds like it doesn't sound exceptional
听起来像它 听起来并不例外
Alexa play the fat rat and this is just
Alexa扮演胖老鼠，这只是
startling songs by the fat rat so Amazon
亚马逊让 胖老鼠的歌声惊人
music right
音乐吧
[Music]
[音乐]
Alexa what song is this this is unity
Alexa 这是什么歌这是团结
from unity by the fat rat again
从肥胖老鼠的统一
[Music]
[音乐]
if you sense the difference I am on the
如果你感觉到我的差异
shore they say yes usually I can't tell
岸边 他们说是的，我通常说不出来
it's great Alexis said go to five
这是伟大的亚历克西斯说去五
[Music]
[音乐]
give instructions above the song song a
给歌曲上面的说明a
big fake sign is it not that advanced we
大的 假标志是不是 那么先进我们
can't it's not on the script
不能不在剧本上
okay can request sir john rowe certain
好的可以请求先生john rowe肯定
types of music but it's not gonna be
音乐的类型， 但它不会
royalty free looks we can play
我们可以玩的免版税外观
so here you go okay so face is a little
所以在这里你没事，所以脸有点儿
better on this it certainly has down
更好的是 它肯定有所 下降
face yeah you're right I was feeling it
面对是的你是对的 我感觉到了
right away yeah okay it's not a
马上 就好，这不是一个
subwoofer
低音炮
but that's it I've got one of these
但就是这样， 我 有其中一个
devices will connect to a Bluetooth
设备将连接到蓝牙
subwoofer the Alexa devices I said it
超低音扬声器我说 的 Alexa设备
the Amazon echo will connect to their
亚马逊回声将连接到他们的
own proprietary like they have a
他们拥有自己的专有权
subwoofer yeah for these devices yeah
低音炮对于这些 设备是啊
okay Alexa stop the music so both of
好的Alexa停止音乐所以两个
them were able to respond to that and do
他们能够对此作出反应 并 做到
a great job of playing a request by
很好地 发挥了一个请求
artist name okay okay I'm kind of
艺术家 的名字还好还好我有点
bouncing around but what's the range of
弹跳但是范围是什么
picking a voice the the Google device I
选择Google设备的声音我
find you do have to be pretty close to
发现你必须非常接近
okay you can't have it across the room
好吧， 你不能 在 房间里
it definitely won't pick you up if
如果，它肯定不会接你
you're upstairs and calling down the
你在楼上叫下来
stairs to it the Amazon echo on the
台阶上的亚马逊呼应着它
other hand I can be anywhere and really
另一方面，我可以在任何地方，真的
and as long as as long as I can pretty
只要我 可以漂亮
much hear you they can hear me and can I
很多人听到他们可以听到我 ， 我 可以
head over that way and do you want to
走过那 条路，你想要吗？
give it a try
试试看
yeah okay okay I don't know do you want
是的没关系， 我不知道 你想要什么
to go stand in the bathroom way over
站在浴室里走过去
there Jeff and just just speak out and
杰夫，只是说出来
ask it to turn on the light so I'm
要求它把 灯打开 ，所以我
waiting I'm like what a good 30 feet
等我好像30英尺
away yeah okay Alexa play me something
离开是的好Alexa 给我带来了一些东西
from fat rat I can't find songs by fat
从胖老鼠我找不到胖子的歌
rat it's the fat rat but turn on the
老鼠它是肥胖的老鼠，但打开了
light okay turn okay Alexa turn on the
光好的转好了Alexa打开了
light
光
Alexa turn on the light okay he's quite
Alexa 打开灯好吧他很好
a ways over there now
那边的方式
can you try to have the Google device
你可以尝试使用谷歌设备吗？
turn off the light
关掉灯
okay Google turn off the light sure so
好吧谷歌关灯确实如此
they both responded so that's okay
他们都回应了所以没关系
that's all right I just have a
没关系，我只是有一个
commanding voice yeah I have found that
指挥声音是啊我发现了
the Amazon device has been more
亚马逊设备已经更多了
sensitive and that's that's been
这是敏感的
impressive okay we're gonna do a quick
令人印象深刻， 好吧，我们要快点做
reminder so Alexa remind me in five
提醒所以Alexa在五点提醒我
minutes to make coffee okay I'll remind
分钟让咖啡好吧 我会提醒的
you in five minutes
你在五分钟之内
okay Google remind me in five minutes to
好吧 谷歌 在五 分钟内 提醒 我
make coffee
做咖啡
sure I'll remind you at 8:10 p.m. okay
我肯定会在晚上8:10提醒你好的
so keep in mind now in five minutes
所以 现在 请 记住五分钟
we're going to hear from both of these
我们将听到 这 两个
devices which one is going to be the one
一个将成为一个的设备
that impresses us okay all right okay
这给我们留下了印象， 好吧 没关系
Google what's the forecast today tonight
谷歌 今晚的预测是什么
and Barry its predicted to be - - in
而 巴里的预测是 - 在
cloudy right now it's - - in cloudy
现在 是阴天 - 在阴天
Alexa what's the forecast today
Alexa 今天的预测是什么
currently in Barry it's minus one
目前在巴里， 它是减去一个
degrees Celsius with cloudy skies
摄氏度与多云的 天空
tonight you can expect snow flurries
今晚你可以期待雪花
with a low of minus three degrees both
两者都 低至 零下三度
of them did really well in that but they
他们做了非常出色的 那个 ，但他们
gave different results so what this
这给了不同的结果
weather where did they put it was five
天气他们 把它放在 哪里 是五
seconds apart and the weather changes I
几秒钟，天气变化我
was gonna barbecue and I was the when is
我要烧烤了， 我就是时候了
the Sun gonna go down and I thought hey
太阳下山了，我觉得嘿
here's the question for okay Google what
这是谷歌好的问题
time is the Sun gonna go down in Barry
时间是太阳 落在巴里
the Sun will set at 4:40 p.m. so I was
太阳将在下午4:40开始，所以我是
like okay well I got to get outside it's
好吧，好吧， 我得到了 它的外面
getting late Alexa what time is the Sun
Alexa已经太晚了
gonna set in Barry Barry sunset would be
在巴里巴里夕阳会集将
439 p.m. so okay
下午 439 ，好吧
right again we hear that the response
我们再次听到了回应
from the Amazon device is very succinct
来自亚马逊的设备非常简洁
like I would answer a question right
就像我会回答一个问题吧
it's not repeating back to me okay all
它不是重复 还给我好吗 所有
right let's do some simple math okay
正确的，让我们做一些 简单的数学 好吗
Alexa what's five times 32 divided by
Alexa什么是32倍除以
two the answer to your calculation is
两个 你的计算 答案 是
eighty okay Google
八十 好吧谷歌
what's five times 32 divided by two
什么是五次32除以 二
it's thinking yeah the lights are going
它的想法是，灯光正在进行中
Oh looks like there's a problem
哦 看起来 有问题
okay Google what's five times 32 / - the
好吧谷歌什么是五次32 /  -
answer is 80 okay a little quicker that
回答是80 还好一点
time so it had to trouble yeah
时间所以也只好 麻烦呀
connecting what about some like let's
连接一些像let的东西
throw a dot five in there Alexa what's
在那里扔一个 五 点 Alexa是什么
five times thirty-two point 5 divided by
通过 五次 32点 5分
two the answer to your calculation is
两个 你的计算 答案 是
eighty one point two five
八十一点二五
notice again I'm just talking to it like
再次注意我只是在谈论 它
I'm not having to like the old days
我不必喜欢过去的日子
where voice recognition didn't work very
其中， 语音识别没有工作 很
is now it's like I'm just talking to it
现在就像我只是在谈论 它
as normal okay Google what is five times
像往常一样好谷歌 是五次
thirty two point five divided by two
三十二点五分两
the answer is eighty one point two five
答案是八十一分二五
okay yeah so pretty quick too to answer
好耶所以相当 快 得 回答
so that's good Alexa how much does an
这样的 Alexa有多 好
amazon.com let go dot second-generation
amazon.com 放开 第二代
black its $19.99 on Amazon after $20 in
黑色 的$ 19.99在亚马逊 之后$ 20
savings if you'd like to hear details
如果你想 听到细节，可以节省开支
just ask so I don't want to give you the
只是问，所以我不想给你
price because the price around the world
价格因为世界各地的价格
is different right and so on we're here
是不同的 ， 所以我们在 这里
yeah that's much different but I want to
是的，那是非常不同的，但我想
show okay obviously we expect the Amazon
显示没问题显然我们 期待亚马逊
device to be good at telling us those
设备善于告诉我们那些
kinds of things but we can also say ok
各种各样的东西，但我们也可以说好
Google how much is an amazon.com on the
谷歌 有 多少是amazon.com上
website techradar.com they say the
他们说 网站techradar.com
Amazon echo dot third-generation is
亚马逊echo dot 第三代是
available now for 49 pounds and 99 pence
现在可用于49磅 和99便士
for $49.99 for $79 yeah I think that was
只需49.99美元，79美元， 我认为那是
different currencies yes Amazon's giving
不同的货币是亚马逊的 给予
me a discount yeah I noticed that it's
我打折啊，我注意到， 它的
given me a better price so both of them
给了我一个更好的价格所以他们两个
answered the question yeah Alexa find a
回答了问题，Alexa发现了一个问题
Starbucks near me I found a Starbucks
我附近的星巴克我找到了星巴克
it's 1.5 miles away on Yonge Street and
距离央街有 1.5英里
Barry it's currently closed but will be
巴里它目前已关闭，但 将会
open tomorrow tomorrow a.m. to 8:00 p.m.
明天 上午 8点到晚上8点开放
okay they're closed so that doesn't help
好吧，他们已经关闭， 所以这没有帮助
me
我
okay Google now find a Starbucks near me
好吧谷歌现在找到 我 附近 的 星巴克
I found a few places within six point
我 在六点内 找到了几个地方
nine kilometers
九公里
the first one is Starbucks at 389 Yonge
第一个是星巴克389 Yonge
Street bear
街 熊
the second one is Starbucks at 179 live
第二个是星巴克在179 直播
8 way Barry
8路巴里
the third one is Starbucks at 76 Barry
第三个是76 Barry的星巴克
view drive Barry okay so they both did
查看驾驶 Barry好， 所以他们 都做到了
great fun yeah I don't say the fact that
非常有趣的是的，我就不多说了事实
it mentioned kilometres is yeah
它提到千米是啊
arresting compared to miles reference
逮捕与英里参考相比
isn't that interesting so I have the
不是那么有趣所以我有
graphic issue so I have to say Alexa how
图形问题所以我不得不说Alexa如何
long will it take me to get to Starbucks
我需要多长时间才能到达星巴克
I found a Starbucks
我找到 了星巴克
it's 1.5 miles away and result in not
它距离1.5英里，导致 没有
based on current traffic it'll take
基于当前的流量，它将采取
about six minutes to drive there okay
大约六分钟的车程就可以了
okay so it matters how you ask the
好的， 所以 问你怎么问
question ok Google how long will it take
问题 好 谷歌需要多 长时间
me to get a Starbucks the closest
我最接近星巴克
Starbucks is at 620 Yonge Street very on
星巴克是在620 Yonge街道上 很
it will take you three minutes to get
它会 带你三分钟搞定
there by car and current traffic I've
我乘车和目前的交通
sent the directions to your phone that's
将指示发送到您的手机
this is a reminder oh there are some
这是一个提醒 哦，有一些
reminders okay Amazon just told me make
提醒好的 亚马逊刚刚告诉我
coffee mm-hmm there's a reminder but the
咖啡mm-hmm有提醒 但是
a counted done the echo did sorry yeah
一个计数完成 的回声很抱歉是的
this is a reminder meet coffee
这是提醒咖啡
Alexa thank you
Alexa 谢谢你
no worries the the Google device didn't
不用担心谷歌设备没有
tell me what the reminder was no that's
告诉我提醒的不是那个
discreet okay Google yes what's the
谨慎 好的谷歌 是的，是什么
reminder hi you have two reminders if
提醒嗨你 有两个提醒，如果
you'd like to hear the details you can
你想 听听 细节，你可以
give me permission in the Google home
在 Google主页上 允许我
app oh look for personal results under
应用程序哦寻找个人结果下
the settings for this device they're
他们是这个设备 的设置
being very careful - you can see the
非常小心 - 你可以看到
details on your phone to get these
手机上的详细信息， 以获取这些
notifications on an iPhone cancel okay
iPhone 上的通知 取消正常
so I can't really judge that because
所以我无法真正判断 ，因为
maybe they're protecting my privacy but
也许他们保护我的隐私但是
at the same time I've already activated
同时我已经激活了
the device on her account I've given it
她给 我的帐户上的设备
the authorization to use I asked for the
授权使用我要求的
command on the device so I would say
我会说，在设备上的命令
that that's a fail so I would say Alexa
这是一个失败所以我会说Alexa
won that one Thank You Alexa
赢了那一个谢谢Alexa
she's so confused now because I said the
她现在很困惑， 因为我说过
name Alexa cancel alright so let's try a
Alexa的名字好吗 取消 所以让我们尝试
couple more okay both told me how long
情侣 更好 还告诉我多久
it's gonna take to Starbucks even though
即便如此，它还会带给星巴克
Google races yes okay Google
谷歌 竞争是好的谷歌
sing me a song what the fun stuff that
给我唱一首有趣的东西
it'll do for it gets canceled cool the
它会为它取消凉爽的
day I can sing Alexa sing me a song
那天我可以唱Alexa给我唱一首歌
[Music]
[音乐]
Alexa canceled I have no idea whether
Alexa 取消了我不知道是否
it's royalty-free or not both of your
它是免版税的，或者不是你的两个
win how in the world do they take the
赢得他们如何在世界上采取
speech software and make it
语音软件并制作它
melodic Melodyne auto-tune isn't that
旋律 Melodyne自动调谐不是那个
amazing
惊人
Wow about Shimogamo and auto-tune the
哇关于Shimogamo 和自动调整
news and how they take the the spoken
新闻以及他们如何接受口述
word and turn it into music it's
单词并把它变成音乐吧
incredible technology they can do that
他们可以做到这一点令人难以置信
okay so next up let's try shopping so
好了，接下来 让我们尝试 这样 的购物
we're gonna go shopping let's add
我们要去购物让我们添加
something to our list okay okay
我们的名单上的东西还可以
yes you want give it a try ask the
是的你想 试试看
Google device
谷歌设备
okay Google eye cookies to my shopping
好吧谷歌 眼睛饼干到我的购物
list okay i gotted cookies to your
列表好吧我给你的饼干
shopping list okay well I already bought
购物清单好吧 我已经 买了
cookies so get it off your list
饼干，所以从列表中删除它
oh okay Google remove cookies from my
哦好吧 谷歌删除我的饼干
shopping list
购物清单
unfortunately I can't remove items from
不幸的是，我不能删除的项目
your shopping list yet to manage your
您的购物清单尚未管理您的
list please use the shopping list in the
列表请使用中的购物清单
Google home app so I have to actually go
谷歌家庭应用程序，所以我必须真正去
into the app in order to remove
进入 应用程序 以删除
something from my list okay Jeff
我列表中的东西好吧杰夫
try to order add to my my shopping list
尝试订购添加到我的购物 清单
on the Alexa device okay Alexa can you
Alexa的设备上，页面没关系，你可以
add eggnog to my shopping list I've
将蛋酒添加到我的购物清单中
added eggnog to your shopping list okay
将蛋酒添加到你的购物清单好吧
I have lots of eggnog at home can you
我家里有很多蛋酒可以
you can never have enough ice pick that
你永远不会有足够的 冰块
off your list Alexa can you take eggnog
在你的名单上Alexa，你可以采取蛋酒
off my shopping list I've checked off
我的购物清单上已经检查过了
eggnog from your shopping list okay
你的购物清单中的蛋酒好吧
Alexa will do it Google will not Alexa
Alexa会这样做Google 不会 Alexa
cancel
取消
thank you final test is to do with
谢谢你最后的测试是做的
temperature so I want to know okay
温度所以我想 知道好的
Google
谷歌
what's the temperature outside the
什么是外面的温度
current temperature in Barry is -2 okay
巴里目前的气温是 -2 好吧
okay Google what's the temperature
谷歌 什么是温度 好吧
inside it's currently 24 degrees it's a
在它内部目前是24度它是 一个
Celsius
摄氏
don't you worry Alexa what's the
难道你不担心Alexa是什么
temperature outside right now it's minus
外面的温度现在 是零下
1 degrees tonight expect a low of minus
今晚1度 预计低点减去
3 two more details Alexa what's the
3 另外两个 细节Alexa是什么
temperature inside inside it's 24 okay
里面的温度 是24好吧
that's warm so it is nice in here right
这很温暖， 所以在 这里 很好
Becca likes it toasty oh that's actually
贝卡喜欢它烤面包哦， 这其实
communicating through my account with my
通过我的帐户与我的帐户沟通
nest device Oh
巢装 哦
my house it's warm in here too it's
我的房子在这里也很温暖
comfortable here okay cuz there's like
这里很舒服好吧因为这样
24 I'm goin there's no way this is 20
24我在 那里这 不可能是20岁
this is 24 24 I would say wow we digress
这 是24 24我会说哇我们离题了
easily don't wait it's like 21 in here
很容易不要等待它就像21在这里
man so opinions of these devices I'd
男人，所以这些设备的意见我
love to hear from you comment below I
我很乐意听到 你的评论
hope that this has been a little bit of
希望这一直 是 一点点
unveiling for you which one is going to
为你揭开哪一个
be best now what is my personal opinion
现在最好的是我个人的 意见
I thought I was gonna really and even
我以为 我会真的 ，甚至
the first day I thought it was gonna
第一 天，我以为它会
lean toward the Google device it seemed
似乎倾向于谷歌设备
very responsive it does a really good
非常敏感，它确实非常好
job of interpreting my questions whereas
解释我的问题，而就业
the the Amazon device would would tend
亚马逊设备会倾向于
to stumble over some of my questions
偶然发现我的一些问题
more often but as I'm learning how to
更常见，但正如我正在学习如何
ask those questions I'm finding that the
问那些我发现的问题
sound quality of the Amazon device is
亚马逊设备的 音质 是
actually really making me lean that way
实际上真的让我倾向于那样
the other thing that I do is I take my
我做 的另一件事 是我接受我的
devices all over the place mm-hmm so I
设备所有的 地方毫米，嗯 ，所以我
took both of these devices as I
采取这两种 设备 ， 因为我
mentioned from home having used them at
从家里提到他们曾经使用过它们
home to work okay having taken it to
回家工作还好吧
work the Amazon echo dot in the app I
在应用程序I中处理Amazon echo dot
can change the Wi-Fi connectivity so
可以改变Wi-Fi连接
that it accesses the Wi-Fi at work right
它 可以在工作 时 访问Wi-Fi
the Google home many on the other hand
另一方面，Google家庭很多
having brought it from home too
已经从家里带来的太
to work it wouldn't allow me to connect
工作它不允许我连接
it said that I'm not on the same Wi-Fi
它说我 不在同一个Wi-Fi上
network so I looked into it and I
网络，所以我调查了 它和我
actually have to remove the device
实际上必须删除 该 设备
completely and reactivate it if I want
完全重新激活它，如果我想
it's unbelievable so but a workaround to
这是令人难以置信的，但一个变通办法
that is at home so I took it home that
那是在 家里，所以我把它带回家了
night and at home I can delete the Wi-Fi
晚上和家里我可以删除Wi-Fi
network then the next day I took it to
网络然后第二天 我把 它带到了
work and I added the Wi-Fi network at
工作，我 添加了Wi-Fi网络
work so now it's able to connect at work
工作所以现在它能够 在工作中连接
but then before I leave work I have to
但在我离开工作之前，我必须这样做
remember delete the Wi-Fi network
记得删除Wi-Fi网络
otherwise I will not be able to connect
否则我将无法连接
at home that's not good that's annoying
在家里这不好，这很 烦人
the Amazon device however I brought that
亚马逊设备然而我带来了
home then having set it up at work and
然后 在家 已经将它设置在工作和
it automatically now connected to my
它现在自动连接到我的
home network so it remembered the
家庭网络所以它记住了
settings for both networks just like my
两个网络的设置就像我一样
phone does right and was able to connect
手机做得对，能够连接
anywhere I went and then I brought it to
我去的任何地方然后我把它 带到了
the studio and I went through the same
工作室和我经历了同样的事情
headache where the Google device I had
我有谷歌设备的头痛
to first delete the network in order to
先删除网络以
be able to connect it here at the studio
能够 在工作室 连接它
and the Amazon device I was able to just
和亚马逊设备我能 刚
add another Wi-Fi network and connect it
添加另一个Wi-Fi网络并连接它
and it was roblem so those are some
它是 roblem所以这些是一些
thoughts to ponder I found the Amazon
思考我发现了亚马逊
device to be more user-friendly but both
设备更加用户友好， 但两者兼而有之
do a very good job and as you know they
做了很好的工作 ，因为你知道他们
both control my lights they both do all
他们都控制我的灯都做了
that kind of stuff and keep in mind this
那种 东西，记住这一点
is a different device so the ability to
是一个不同的设备所以能力
control devices that's a separate device
控制设备是一个单独的设备
I don't put a link for you below and you
我 下面 没有 给 你 链接 和你
can you can check that out as well
你可以可以检查出来 ， 以及
they're not expensive but you can get
他们不贵，但你可以得到
all these smart home devices so so post
所有这些智能家居设备如此贴心
your opinions we'd appreciate that now
你的意见 我们 现在 很感激
with it being connected to your Wi-Fi
它连接 到您的Wi-Fi
and maybe you don't have the answer to
也许你没有 答案
this could you set it up like will the
这可能您设置 等等 将在
devices read what's being transmitted
设备读取正在传输的内容
through your network for instance I'm
通过你的网络，例如我
thinking you've got NEMS
以为你有NEMS
could you create some sort of a report
你能创建某种报告吗？
within Em's that is automatically to be
在Em的 内部自动成为
pulled from the devices so you could say
你可以说， 从 设备中拉出来
you know hey what is being asked of the
你知道嘿，被问到了什么
device yeah like you could say can you
设备是的，你可以说你能
give me a network yeah within those and
在那些 和 我之间给我一个网络
it goes all if yeah like Amazon calls it
如果亚马逊称之为它，那就完全可以了
skills I'm not sure about Google how
我不确定Google的技能如何
they work a similar kind of thing okay
他们工作类似的东西没关系
you activate it like a like an app okay
你像一个应用程序一样激活它好吧
the kids activated the fart skill so
孩子们激活了屁技能
Alexa and they figured it out Alexa
Alexa和他们认出了Alexa
sorry yeah
对不起， 是的
Alexa canceled yeah so these are skills
Alexa 取消了，所以这些都是技能
that you add so if I create it so being
您添加的，所以如果我创建它 是如此
the developer of names to answer the
开发者的名字来回答
question flat out if I created a skill
如果我创造了一项技能，问题就会消失
and uploaded it to Amazon store then you
然后将它上传到亚马逊 商店
could request that skill I am working on
可以要求我正在努力的技能
one for category five that's okay it
一个类别 五，这 没关系
ultimately why I got these two devices
最终为什么我得到这两个设备
aside okay I'll up these these skills
除此之外，我会提升这些技能
for these devices so you can listen to
对于这些设备， 你 可以听
our podcasts and things like that on
我们的播客和 类似的东西
these devices so yes if they exist okay
这些设备如果它们存在就可以了
does that help it's amazing that a fart
这对屁有多么惊人
is a skill apparently it is important
显然是一项技能很 重要
that my resume and Alexa diet skills
我的简历和Alexa的 饮食技巧
okay so do we have time to talk about
好了，我们 是否有时间谈
privacy or are we out of time
隐私还是我们没时间了
well what do you want to know like I I
那么你想知道什么像II
can't bring myself to purchase one of
无法让自己购买其中之一
these okay like if I was to go buy one
这些还好，如果我去买一个
you're afraid of Big Brother not only
你不仅害怕老大哥
that I'm just afraid of my data
我只是害怕我的数据
collection okay like if I was to buy one
收藏好的，如果我要买一个
100% I would go with Amazon echo um just
100％我与亚马逊去呼应嗯 刚
based on today alone like I'm sold that
仅仅基于今天就像我卖掉 那样
that's where I go but I don't like the
我去的地方， 但我不喜欢
idea of it listening all the time even
它的想法甚至一直在听
like it could sit there all day and I
像它可以整天坐在那里，我
could never say her name but it's gonna
永远不会说出她的名字，但它会
listen the whole time but you do get
听一听，但你确实得到了
used you get used to walking in the room
用 你习惯走 在 房间里
and saying Alexa play the fat rat
并说Alexa扮演肥胖的老鼠
shuffling songs by the fat Wow and then
由肥胖的Wow拖着歌 然后
turns on music and you reach out and now
打开音乐 ，你 现在 伸出手
Alexa Alexa Alexa Alexa you do get used
Alexa Alexa Alexa Alexa 你习惯了
to that especially when you've got kids
特别是 当你有 孩子的时候
running around and there doesn't mean
跑来跑去，并不意味着
likes not listening
喜欢不听
it is not listening but I'm still not
它不是在听，但我还没有
convinced Alexis stop the music the fact
说服亚历克西斯停止音乐这一事实
that if you don't think about it that's
如果你不这么想的话
that's what I struggle with like I don't
就像我没有那样 ，这就是我所挣扎的
activate the the voice controls for my
激活我的语音控件
phone I refuse to do it because I don't
电话我拒绝这样做 ，因为 我不这样做
like the idea of it always listening to
喜欢 它 的想法 总是听
me so dumb you know what is your the
我这么傻你知道你的是什么
microphone but what is the privacy
麦克风， 但隐私是什么
protections on these like because I know
对这些的保护就像我知道的那样
what like you hear stories where and I
你和我在哪里听到的故事
want to say was covered not necessarily
想要说的不一定
in the news for us but about a month ago
在新闻中，但大约一个月前
there was somebody there was a home
有人有一个家
invasion and the person didn't activate
入侵和人没有激活
their device but it still heard the
他们的设备，但它仍然听到了
distress and called the police
遇险并打电话报警
well before the show you were telling
在 你讲 的节目 之前
that story and you said it's name call
这个故事 ， 你说这是名字 叫
the police it started dialing and I had
警察开始拨号，我有
to halt it yes because if you if you
停止是的，因为如果你，如果你
state it then yeah I will it will do
说它然后是的我会这样做
that
那
careful with your word and so what
小心你的话，等等
you're very helpful it can be very very
你是非常有帮助的也可以 是非常非常
helpful in a case like that
在这样的情况下有所帮助
sure it can which is wonderful but I
确定它可以是多么 美妙但 我
just it's I don't know there's something
只是它我不知道有什么
in me I'm like I just can't do it I'm
在我，我喜欢我不能做到 这一点，我
it's the fact that everything is being
一切都在存在
listened to I just I can't I can't
听我说我 不能不能
mentally get put it there until you say
精神上把它放在那里， 直到你说
the key word there's not there's no
关键词不存在没有
transaction happening and the
交易发生和
transaction is what I say after the key
交易就是我说的关键
word but it's not about the transaction
但这不是关于交易的
it's the fact that it's right now it's
这是事实，它现在是它的
still listening because it's waiting for
还在听，因为它在等待
the name to be called but what's it
要调用的名称， 但它是什么
doing with that data it's not that's the
做 这些数据 并不是那样的
question that's exactly why Jeff that
这个问题就是为什么杰夫
these devices you can't change their
这些设备你无法改变他们的
name to Bob Alexa change your name to
Bob Alexa的名字改为你的名字
Bob sorry I can only help change the way
鲍勃抱歉， 我只能帮助改变方式
grow to one of these Amazon computer or
成长为 这些亚马逊电脑之一或
echo 3 options okay because in it's very
echo 3选项还可以， 因为它非常好
very finite system that is built into
非常有限的系统内置
this because you're thinking that the
这是因为你在想
cloud is always listening to you know
云总是在听 你的消息
the device is listening for those three
该设备正在监听 这三个
key words so it is here in my network
关键词所以它在我的网络中
waiting for those key words as soon as I
我尽快 等待那些 关键词
activate it with the key word now the
现在用关键词激活它
cloud is activated and waiting for my
云被激活并等待我的
command
命令
so when I asked for the weather forecast
所以当我问 天气预报
that request goes out to the cloud and
该 请求转发到云端
is translated and then sent back
翻译后发回
instantaneously I still don't buy it
瞬间 我还是 不买账
and maybe I'm just being skeptical
也许我只是 怀疑
you're skeptical afraid of technology in
你怀疑害怕技术的
the future and possibly a little
未来 ，可能还有一点
conspiracy theorist
阴谋理论家
oh sure 100% I I know that I have
哦，当然100％我知道我有
conspiracy theory tendencies but it's
阴谋论倾向但它是
the fact that it's always listening
事实上，它总是在倾听
it may not be accessing the club but
它可能不会进入俱乐部但是
it's always listening and I just can't
它总是在听，我不能
help but wonder no it's not listening
帮助 但 不知道不是没有听
Alexa Alexa Alexa Alexa Alexa that's why
Alexa Alexa Alexa Alexa Alexa这就是原因
I love that it does have that button
我喜欢它确实有那个 按钮
because I do have that privacy feature
因为我确实有 这个 隐私功能
and when I'm not using it because I'm
当我不使用它时，因为我
not always using it you don't have to
并不总是 使用它，你不必
leave it on all the time Jeff
永远把它留在 杰夫身上
when I'm not using it well if you are
如果你没有使用它的 话
really that bad unplug the power yeah
真的如此糟糕拔掉 电源耶
come on true I agree oh for goodness
来吧，我同意哦，天哪
sake Jeff I know I I'm sure there's
杰夫，我知道我，我确定有
people watching this they're just like
人们看着他们 就像 他们 一样
why is this guy on a tech show filled
为什么这家伙在 高科技展充满
with plants take out Jeff edit him out
与植物取出杰夫编辑他
let me know your opinions we'd love to
让我 知道你们喜欢的意见
hear from you if you if you have similar
如果你有类似的话，请听你的消息
concerns to Jeff hey post them below and
对杰夫的关注嘿他们发布在下面和
maybe some of the community can react
也许一些社区可以做出反应
and respond to that I have a very
并回应我有一个非常
different mindset in that I trust the
不同的心态，我相信
encryption that is there and I do
我在那里加密
believe that the information that you
相信 信息，你
know I'm asking for the weather I don't
知道我要求天气不要
really I'm surfing the web I'm going on
我正在网上冲浪，我正在上网
the web to get my weather it's no
网络让我的天气不行
different than asking it this way it's
不同于以这种方式询问它
just a different interface yeah you had
只是一个不同的界面，你有
me at like set the reminders I feel like
我喜欢设置 我觉得的提醒
that's Anna and Amazon's device one that
那是安娜和亚马逊的设备之一
one yeah I love that it just hey time to
是的， 我喜欢它只是嘿时间
make coffee yeah I love it I like it let
制作咖啡 是的，我喜欢它，我喜欢它 让
us know your thoughts everybody comment
我们知道你的想法每个人 评论
below make sure you give us a like and a
下面 确保你给我们 一个喜欢和一个
thumbs up and to subscribe if you if you
竖起大拇指并订阅， 如果你，如果你
appreciated this this hopefully unbiased
赞赏这个希望无偏见
comparison links are below again we are
比较链接 再次 在下面 我们是
a partner with Amazon so you're welcome
亚马逊的合作伙伴， 欢迎您的到来
to use our link we'd appreciate that
使用我们的链接，我们很感激
I've also got a link to that device that
我还有一个 指向 该设备 的 链接
I use to turn on and off the light
我用来 开灯和关灯
and we've got a link to the Google home
我们有一个链接到谷歌的家
Mini as well although they're not a
迷你也是如此， 虽然 它们不是
partner so we don't get a cut of that so
合作伙伴，所以我们没有得到这方面的一个切口 ，以便
don't buy it
不要买它
totally kidding you make up your own
完全开玩笑你自己组成
mind all right Sasha yeah we're gonna
介意没事 萨沙是啊，我们要去
head right over to the news room are you
头部正上方 的新闻会客厅是你
ready for it certainly a.m. awesome here
准备好它肯定在 这里 很棒
are the stories were covering this week
在故事】 本周覆盖
in the category 5 TV newsroom Google's
在类别 5电视 新闻室谷歌
parent company alphabet will test its
母公司字母表 将测试它
drone delivery service in Finland next
接下来 在 芬兰的无人机送货服务
year Microsoft edge is dead seriously
一年微软边缘严重死亡
Microsoft is building its own chromium
微软正在建立自己的铬
browser to replace the default on
浏览器替换默认值
Windows 10 Google is expediting the
Windows 10 Google正在加速推出
closure of Google Plus after another
Google Plus的关闭接连不断
security bug for the second time in
安全漏洞第二次出现
history a human-made object has reached
历史是人造物体所达到的
the space between the stars these
这些 星星之间的空间
stories are coming right up don't go
故事即将到来 不要 去
anywhere
随地
this is the category 5 TV newsroom
这是5 类 电视新闻室
covering the week's top tech stories
涵盖本周的顶级科技故事
slide Linux by us Jeff Westen
由我们杰夫韦斯滕 滑动 Linux
Gemma you're building a brand-new
Gemma你正在 建立一个 全新的
beautiful website what
漂亮的网站是什么
aren't you your terrible actor what does
你不是你 可怕 的演员有哪些呢
where acting comes into play I don't
代理发挥作用我不这样做
know you're supposed to act okay are you
知道 你应该表现 得 好吗？
building a really cool website are you
建立一个非常酷的网站是你
building a really cool website just
建立一个非常酷的网站
because Jeff is confused doesn't mean
因为杰夫 很困惑 并不代表
you have to be visit cap five dot TV
你必须访问 五点电视 帽
slash dream host to sign up for
签名梦想主持人报名参加
unlimited web hosting for your website
为您的网站 无限制的虚拟主机
with unlimited email accounts MySQL
无限的电子邮件 帐户的MySQL
databases the latest version of PHP
数据库最新版本的PHP
WordPress and more and even a free
WordPress和更多，甚至是免费的
domain name registration it's less than
域名注册少于
six dollars per month so sign up today
每月六块钱 ，所以 今天 报名
cat five dot TV slash dream host I'm
猫五 点电视斜线梦想主持人我是
Sasha Rickman and here are the top
Sasha Rickman和这里是顶级的
stories were following this week
故事发生在本周之后
Google's parent company alphabet will
谷歌的母公司字母表将会
test its drone delivery service in
测试其无人机送货服务
Finland next year Helsinki will be the
芬兰明年赫尔辛基将成为
first European location for wing which
第一个欧洲机翼的位置
has been testing drones in Australia
一直在澳大利亚测试无人机
it's aircraft will deliver packages
它的 飞机将提供包裹
weighing up to 1.5 kilograms within a
体重可达1.5公斤
minute of being an order being placed
的作为 一个顺序分钟被放置
several companies including wing and
几家公司， 包括翼和
Amazon are developing drone delivery
亚马逊正在开发无人机交付
services but they have spent years in
服务， 但他们已经花了几年时间
development without launching in
发展没有发动
December 2013 Amazon chief executive
2013年12月亚马逊首席执行官
Jeff Bezos predicted his company's
杰夫贝索斯预测他的公司
primary delivery service would launch
主要递送服务将启动
within five years however its service is
在五年 内， 它的服务是
still in development wing said its
还在开发中的翼说
drones had made 55,000 journeys in
无人机已经完成了55,000次 旅行
Australia delivery items such as
澳大利亚的送货项目如
medicine coffee and household goods it
药咖啡和家居用品 呢
said it had chosen fiddlin for its
说，它已选择fiddlin 其
European trial because Finnish people
欧洲审判因为芬兰人
were renowned for being early adopters
以早期采用者而闻名
of new technologies it has invited them
它邀请了他们的新技术
to share what products they would like
分享他们想要的产品
to see delivered by drone with
要查看无人机交付
suggestions including breakfast lunch
建议包括早餐午餐
painkillers and household essentials
止痛药和家庭必需品
customers will be able to place an order
客户将能够下订单
using a smartphone app and the drone
使用智能手机应用程序和无人机
delivery will be offered free of charge
送货服务免费
during the trial period for drone
在无人机试用期间
delivery services to be viable the
送货服务是可行的
technology Giants must show that their
技术巨人必须表明他们的
drones are safe and reliable critics
无人机是安全可靠的 评论家
also question whether the public will
也质疑 公众 是否 愿意
want noisy drones delivering goods in
想要嘈杂的无人机送货
towns and cities but wing says drone
城镇和城市，但翼说无人机
delivery
交货
safer faster and more environmentally
更安全，更环保
friendly than ground delivery wing is
比地面交 付翼友好
part of alphabets other vets division
部分字母其他兽医师
which includes self-driving car project
其中包括自动驾驶汽车项目
way mo an internet delivery balloon
莫方式的互联网分发气球
maker loon okay okay yeah so wing
制造商loon 没关系，是的， 所以翼
interest I like it I love the concept of
兴趣我喜欢我的爱情观
being able to get something that quickly
能够 迅速 得到一些东西
yeah within one minute of order accident
是的，在订单意外的一分钟内
that we're setting on you can't cancel
我们正在设置你无法取消
one artery bad yeah that was my first
一条动脉坏了是的，这是我的第一次
autumn like a minute yeah like so it
秋天像一分钟，是的 ，所以它
goes in the order goes in is it somebody
按顺序进去是否有人
on the other end that's going on workers
另一端是 工人
yeah like that's just ridiculous one
是的，那只是荒谬的
minute intense I would say you know you
分钟激烈 我会说你认识 你
know within like half an hour of your
知道你的半小时内
order being processed like what happens
订单处理就像发生的事情
if there's an error you're right you
如果有错误你是对的
can't return it but what I can't help
不能回来但是我无能为力
but wonder though is does this open the
但奇怪的是，这是否打开了
door to you know some guy sitting on his
门口你知道有人坐在 他 身上
porch again looks like a nice package
门廊再次看起来像一个很好的包
take our advice it's like I'm stealin
接受我们的建议，就像我是 斯大林
that yeah GPS is gonna help with that
那 是的GPS是要去帮助与
though yeah yeah that's true I mean
虽然是的，我的意思是真的
you'll see it come down the Amazon
你会看到它来自 亚马逊
drones are armed with missiles I wish
我希望无人驾驶飞机装备导弹
that we were testing it here well we
我们在这里测试它 很好
should be testing it here because we
应该在这里测试，因为 我们
have interesting weather I was gonna say
我会说 有趣的天气
probably couldn't handle Canadian
可能无法 处理加拿大人
weather not if they're battery operated
天气不是 如果他们是电池操作
that I would like for it to be able to
我想它 能够
handle it and I would like to be able to
处理它， 我希望能够
order something and have it delivered
订购一些东西 并 交付
within one minute like the time that my
在一分钟内，就像我的时间
dear and it takes off within a minute
亲爱的，它在一 分钟 内起飞
yes it'll only take a few minutes I ran
是的，我只需要几分钟 就跑了
out of toner the other day
前几天没有碳粉
and had to drive across town because uh
因为 呃 ，我不得不开车穿过小镇
my project was due and town is big when
我的项目是由于和镇大 当
you're panicking and it's close to sex
你是恐慌，它接近 性
and everything's closing but had I known
一切都在结束， 但我 知道了
a drone was just gonna deliver it how
一架无人机就是如何实现它的
they feel your toner I'm excited about
他们觉得你的碳粉 我很兴奋
breakfast lunch and pain come on guys
早餐午餐和痛苦来了
lunch so you're done
午餐，所以你完成了
or lock you're out breakfast lunch and
或锁定你早餐午餐和
painkillers it would be I know they
止痛药，我知道他们
talked about household items but it
谈到家居用品但它
would be interesting to see how they get
会很有趣 ，看看他们是如何 得到的
into things like controlled substances
像受控物质这样的东西
like would they open the door to say hey
就像他们打开门说嘿
you want to buy your alcohol you know
你想买你知道的酒
you can purchase it through us we're
你可以通过我们购买我们
gonna drone delivery where's the social
无人机送货的地方是社交
responsibility in that like there's
像那样的 责任
there's a placed on the person
这个人有一个位置
purchasing right but do you think
购买权，但你认为
that'll happen though we'll see maybe
虽然我们会看到也许会发生这种情况
maybe maybe not I don't even steps
也许不是我甚至没有步骤
because there's a lot of things that
因为那里有很多 东西
come with it where it's like how are you
来吧，就像 你 怎么样
gonna handle the control issue of you
要处理你的控制问题
know age-restricted products so does
知道受年龄限制的 产品也是如此
amazon have to start being that
亚马逊必须开始这样做
bartender who says look guy we're
酒保谁说看我们的家伙
cutting you off this is the sixth beer
打断你， 这已经是第六啤酒
delivery we've given you tonight right
我们今晚给你送货的权利
cutting you off yeah that's interesting
切断你 是的有趣的
yeah it'll be yeah it'll be neat to see
是的， 是的，它会很好 看
how it develops for sure I would like it
它如何 发展肯定我会喜欢它
here already so finish people finish up
这已经 完成了 人们的完成
your experiment send it on over live up
你的实验 是通过 实时 发送的
to your name
以你的名字命名
Microsoft edge is dead seriously
微软优势 严重
Microsoft is building its own chromium
微软正在建立自己的铬
browser to replace the default on
浏览器替换默认的
Windows 10 the software giant first
Windows 10是软件巨头的第一名
introduced its edge browser three years
介绍其边缘浏览器三年
ago with a redesigned to replace
以前用重新设计 来 取代
Internet Explorer and modernized the
Internet Explorer和现代化的
default browsing experience to compete
默认的浏览体验竞争
with Chrome and others while the modern
与Chrome和其他人一起现代化
look and feel has paid off for edge the
外观已还清 边缘
underlying browser engine edge HTML has
底层浏览器引擎边缘HTML有
struggled to keep up with chromium
努力跟上铬的步伐
Microsoft is finally giving up and
微软终于放弃了
moving its default Windows 10 browser to
将其默认的Windows 10浏览器移动到
chromium apparently there has been a
铬显然有一个
growing frustration inside Microsoft
微软内部越来越沮丧
thanks to edge edges web compatibility
由于边缘网络兼容性
issues and businesses and customers have
问题，企业 和客户都有
been pushing the company to improve
在推动公司改善
things Chrome is now the most popular
Chrome浏览器现在最受欢迎
browser across all devices
所有设备上的浏览器
thanks to androids popularity and the
感谢机器人的普及和
rise of Chrome on PCs and Macs web
PC和Mac 网络上Chrome的崛起
developers have been favoring its one
开发商一直偏爱它
rendering engine to optimize their sites
渲染引擎来优化他们的网站
Google
谷歌
has been creating chrome only web
一直在创建仅限Chrome的网站
services simply because it's often the
服务只是因为它经常是
first to adopt emerging web technologies
首先采用新兴的网络技术
as its engineers contribute to many web
因为它的工程师为许多网络做出贡献
standards Microsoft's rendering engine
标准微软的渲染引擎
has fallen behind as a result and the
因此而落后了
company is finally ready to admit this
公司终于 准备承认这一点
there were signs Microsoft was about to
有微软即将出现的迹象
adopt chromium onto Windows as the
在Windows上采用铬作为
company's engineers have been working
公司的工程师一直在 努力
with Google to support a version of
与谷歌 支持 的 版本
Chrome on an arm powered Windows
用手臂驱动Windows上的Chrome
operating system adopting chromium as
采用铬的操作系统
the default rendering engine for Windows
Windows的默认呈现引擎
10 will end Microsoft's hostility
10将结束微软的敌意
towards chrome Microsoft has regularly
朝着Chrome微软定期
push notifications to Windows 10 users
向Windows 10用户推送通知
to attempt to convince them not to use
试图说服他们 不要使用
Chrome and Microsoft pulled Google
Chrome和微软撤回了谷歌
Chrome's installer from the Windows
来自Windows的 Chrome安装程序
Store because it apparently violated
存储， 因为 它 显然违反了
store policies hello yeah they've been
商店政策你好，他们一直都是
saying - so if you try to install Chrome
说 - 所以如果你尝试 安装Chrome
that will warn you are you sure you want
这会警告你，你确定你想要的
to do this because edge is so much
要做到这一点，因为边缘是如此之多
better
更好
yeah hopefully nobody ever fell for that
是的，希望 没有人为此而堕落
but now how I say oh well we're actually
但现在我怎么说哦，我们实际上是
going to switch roam are you sure you
打算转换 你确定你
want to install this because Chrome is
想安装这个，因为Chrome是
better right
好吧
well Chrome or even choice just don't ya
好的Chrome 甚至选择就是不要
just like here's the facts they the user
就像这里是用户的事实
wants to install Chrome but that aside
想要安装Chrome， 但除此之外
so we had the discussion last week about
所以 我们 上周 讨论 过
how Microsoft is so dead set in their
微软是如何死在他们的
old ways yes and think that hey if we
旧的方式是的，如果我们认为嘿嘿
force users to use edge they will use
强迫用户使用他们将使用的边缘
edge well then the user said you know
边缘好然后用户说你知道
what no we're not using edge give me a
什么不，我们 没有使用边缘给我一个
break mm-hmm
打破mm-hmm
it was a lousy browser to begin with and
这是一个糟糕的浏览器开始和
horrible doesn't support add-ons or
可怕的不支持附加组件或
anything and you you want us to use this
什么，你希望我们 使用它
No all right if my choice was between
如果 我选择的 话，那就没关系 了
Chrome and edge I would always pick room
Chrome和边缘我总是会选择房间
always always 100% of the time always
始终始终100％的时间
there's never time why I'd be like Oh
从来没有时间为什么我会像 哦
Edge has the edge on this one never
Edge 在这一方面具有优势
never ever would I ever say that never
永远不会永远不会说
so finally they've given up and said
所以最后他们放弃了并且说
okay well we're gonna base
好吧，我们要基地
I don't know if it's still gonna be
我不知道它是否还会 存在
called edge or what but it's gonna be
被称为边缘或什么但它会是什么
Chrome at its heart because chromium is
因为铬是铬的核心
the open source project the powers
开源 项目的权力
chrome and is now going to power
铬和现在正在 上台
Microsoft's default browser as well will
微软的默认浏览器 也 将
they call it chromium or Chrome what I
他们称之为铬或铬
don't find interesting and this is like
找不到有趣的， 这就像
a very far offshoot is the fact that was
这是一个很远的分支
it not Microsoft that bought github yeah
不是微软买了github是的
which is all open source stuff so it's
这是所有开源的东西，所以它是
interesting that they buy github which
有趣的是，他们买github 哪个
is about open source now suddenly
现在突然关于开源
they're going to use chromium as the
他们将使用铬作为
base it just makes you wonder if
它只是让你想知道是否
Microsoft is finally gone okay we need
微软终于好了， 我们需要
to release the reins start doing some
释放缰绳开始做一些
open source and see what people can do
开源，看看人们可以做些什么
with our products become a support
用我们的产品成为支持
company yeah and just it'd be
公司是的，就是这样
interesting to see if that's where
有趣的是，看看那是在哪里
they're going and if so what does that
他们会去，如果是这样的话
mean for the future of Microsoft mm-hmm
意味着微软mm-hmm的未来
you know are they going to open up you
你知道他们会打开你吗？
know office suite to be open source
知道办公套件 是开源的
based if they don't change their ways
如果他们不改变他们的方式
then they will I mean I I hate to say it
那么他们我的意思是我讨厌说出来
because it sounds presumptuous and it
因为这听起来很冒昧
sounds prophetic in a way but they go
在某种程度上听起来有预言，但他们走了
down go be found only in past episodes
只有在过去的 剧集中才能找到
this week who just said he's been saying
本周 刚刚说他一直在 说
for years that Amazon will not last
多年来亚马逊不会持续
forever it's going to go down because he
永远它会因为他而下降
said there's about a 30 year shelf-life
说有大约30年的 保质期
on all major companies so I don't
在所有主要公司，所以我没有
Microsoft is out that they're past it
微软指出， 他们过去 吧
well they're there and they're still
好吧，他们在那里，他们 仍然
holding on to old paradigms and they
持有 旧范式和他们
need to get out of that and they're
需要摆脱它，他们是
trying I mean I have to give them that
尝试我的意思是 我必须给他们
they're switching now from edge to
他们现在从边缘切换到
Permian but again they're making big
二叠纪，但他们又变大了
mistakes with regards to everything that
关于一切的错误
they do Windows 10 is the last version
他们做Windows 10是最后一个版本
of Windows we're just going to update it
我们只是要更新它
and every single update for the past
以及过去的 每一次 更新
four months night so people are losing
四个月的夜晚让 人们失败了
faith in the very OS and people are
信心 很OS和人民
saying now we need Windows 11 well know
说现在我们需要Windows 11 知道
Windows 10 is the last Windows they need
Windows 10是他们需要的最后一个Windows
to just get over themselves and move on
只是克服自己，继续前进
mm-hmm is what they need to do and maybe
mm-hmm 是他们需要做的事情
that's what they're doing with chrome
这就是他们 用铬做的事情
they need to just go back to Longhorn No
他们需要回到 Longhorn No.
no job was failure yeah Wow okay Google
没有工作失败呀哇 好吧谷歌
is expediting the closure of Google Plus
正在加快Google Plus的关闭
after yet another security bug
在又 一个 安全漏洞之后
we knew Google+ was shutting down but
我们知道Google+正在关闭 但是
Google has announced that they are
谷歌宣布他们是
expediting this process since a new
自新的以来加快这一进程
security bug was discovered with the
安全漏洞被发现了
Google+ API 50 2.5 million users in
Google+ API 50 250万用户
connection with a Google+ API
与Google+ API的关联
potentially had their name email address
可能有他们的名字电子邮件地址
occupation age and other information
职业年龄和其他 信息
stolen in this latest breach Google is
在这最新的违规行为中被盗谷歌是
moving up the closure of the consumer
提升消费者的关闭
Google+ to April 2019 and closing down
Google+至2019年4月并关闭
all the Google+ API s in the next 90
所有Google+ API都将 在接下来的90年代推出
days Google says we want to give users
天谷歌说我们想给用户
ample opportunity to transition off
过渡的充分机会
consumer Google+ and over the coming
消费者Google+和即将到来的
months we will continue to provide users
几个月 我们将继续为用户提供服务
with additional information including
附加信息包括
ways they can safely and securely
他们 可以安全 和安全的方式
securely download the and migrate their
安全下载并迁移他们的
data yet another Google service to add
数据还有另外一项Google服务要添加
to the graveyard checkout killed by
被墓地结账的人
google.com for the full list we knew it
google.com 获取 我们所知道 的完整列表
was coming I knew when I signed up for
当我报名时，我知道了
Google+ that it was gonna fail really
Google+它 真的 会失败
miserable miserable I don't know that I
悲惨可怜我不知道我
don't know that I signed up for it I
不知道，我注册了它， 我
found as soon as I signed up for it it
一旦 发现 ，我注册了它， 它
was not valid for what I would want yeah
无效，因为 我 想 什么 呀
it was very it was obsolete from the
它 真的 已经过时了
get-go because there was just nothing to
开始， 因为 没有什么可以
make it community based it felt very
让它成为基于社区的感觉非常
circles - I did have it I did have
圈子- 我确实拥有它
Google+ I did have it I think it was a
我确实拥有它我觉得它是一个
failed attempt of kind of like creating
失败的尝试有点像创造
a new type of Facebook yeah social media
一种新型的Facebook 耶社交媒体
and yeah everything else I kind of feel
是的， 我感觉到的 一切
like this is this has been hyped a lot
像这样被炒作了很多
yeah the Google+ shutting down has been
是啊Google+的关停已经
in the media and we're reporting on it
在媒体上，我们正在报道它
as well but it kind of feels like Google
同样， 但 它有点像谷歌
is just they're trying to get rid of it
只是他们正试图 摆脱它
they're trying to and so the there have
他们正在努力，所以那里有
been theories and maybe conspiracy
是理论，也许是阴谋
theories but folks who think that Google
理论， 但人们认为谷歌
is just creating these
只是创造这些
exploits oh that's hilarious that's a
利用哦，这是一个热闹的
great theory so that people lose
伟大的理论让 人们输了
confidence in the platform that they
他们 对平台充满信心
already don't have confidence in because
已经不 具备 ，因为信心
who's gonna care just the people who
谁会关心那些人
have their data on us like three well
他们的数据就好像三个一样
I've got to get my stuff off three
我必须把我的 东西拿走三个
people everybody else in the world is
世界上其他人都是
like who cares if Google+ has been
喜欢谁关心Google+是谁
compromised so they know that and so
妥协， 所以他们知道这一点
they create this fake hey we've been
他们创造了这个假嘿我们一直都是
hacked again well do this to save you
再次黑客攻击这样做是为了拯救你
gone I don't I mean I looked up faith in
走了我不是说我 抬头相信
a company that they wouldn't build their
他们不会建立自己的公司
brand off insecure products no but they
品牌关闭不安全的产品， 但他们
are big enough goggle alphabet are big
足够大的护目镜字母表很大
enough that they can just if they want
他们可以随心所欲
to brush this one they want this one god
刷这个他们想要这个 神
when I get rid of it so they could
当 我摆脱 它，因此他们可能
theoretically do something like that
理论上做这样 的 事情
they could say that because they're who
他们可以说因为他们是谁
cares about that bridge s nobody cares
在乎这些 桥 小号 无人问津
about that breach except the people who
关于那个突破，除了那些 人
have their data on it who now have been
他们的数据现在已经存在
given an opportunity which 90 days of
鉴于其中 90天的机会
which to get what are you actually does
获得你实际 做的是什么
garner like a lot of consumer confidence
获得了很多消费者的信心
like oh they're reporting on their own
就像他们自己报道一样
thing and shutting it down I like them
关闭它 我喜欢它们
yeah you're not gonna fix it because
是的，你 不会解决它， 因为
it's a dead thing yes we're not gonna
它是一个死的东西是的，我们不会
put any work into it we're not gonna
把任何工作投入其中我们都不会
dedicate man-hours to that just like so
把工时献给那样的人
they've got marketing people so using
他们有营销人员如此使用
false hack exploits it's akin to like
虚假黑客利用它类似于
saying I want a new microwave so I'm
说我想要一台新的微波炉，所以我
just gonna throw this tin foil in the
只是要把 这个 锡箔 扔进去
microwave and hit five minutes mm-hmm
微波炉打了五分钟mm-hmm
it's like Sasha throwing her things on
这就像萨莎扔她的东西
the floor to get warned to replace it's
得到警告以取代 它的地板
not on purpose I can't even call them
不是故意的， 我甚至不能 打电话给他们
lines
线
I did it oh I can't get a replacement
我做到 了哦我无法获得替代品
warranty but you can send me a new one
保修，但你可以给我一个新的
because I liked it so much don't go too
因为我喜欢 ，所以 不要 去 太
far down this rabbit hole then you'll
在这个兔子洞的下方， 你会
reveal who we're talking about nobody
揭示我们在谈论谁没人
knows it's completely inside and
知道它完全在里面
completely inside for the second time in
完全在里面第二次进入
history a human-made object has reached
历史是人造物体所达到的
the space between the stars NASA's
美国宇航局的 明星之间的空间
Voyager 2 probe now has exited the
旅行者2号探测器现已退出
heliosphere the protective bubble of
日光层的保护性泡沫
particles and magnetic fields created by
粒子和磁场由
the Sun comparing data from different
太阳比较来自 不同的 数据
instruments abre aboard the trailblazing
在开拓者上空的仪器
spacecraft mission scientists determined
宇宙飞船任务科学家确定
the probe crusts the outer edge of the
探头结壳的外缘
heliosphere on November 5th this
日光层在11月5日这
boundary called the heliopause is
称为日光的边界是
the tenuous hot solar wind meets the
脆弱的热太阳风满足
cold dense interstellar medium its twin
寒冷密集的星际介质它的双胞胎
Voyager 1 crossed this boundary in 2012
旅行者1号 在2012年越过了这个边界
but Voyager 2 carries a working
但旅行者2携带着工作
instrument that will provide
将提供的工具
first-of-its-kind observations of the
最先进的观察
nature of this gateway into the
这个门户进入的性质
interstellar space Voyager 2 now is
星际空间旅行者2现在是
slightly more than eleven billion miles
稍逾十十亿英里的
from Earth mission operators can still
从地球任务运营商仍然可以
communicate with Voyager 2 as it enters
进入后与旅行者2沟通
this new phase of its journey but the
这个旅程的新阶段但是
information moving at the speed of light
信息以 光的 速度移动
takes about 16 point 5 hours to travel
旅行需要大约16点5小时
from the spacecraft to earth
从 飞船 到地球
by comparison light traveling from the
通过比较来自的光
Sun takes about eight minutes to reach
太阳大约需要8分钟 才能到达
Earth together the two voyagers provide
地球上 的两个航海者一起提供
a detailed glimpse of how our
详细了解我们的情况
heliosphere interacts with the constant
日光层与常数相互作用
interstellar wind flowing from beyond
星际风从外面流过
their observations complement data from
他们的观察补充了数据
NASA's interstellar boundary Explorer or
NASA的星际边界资源管理器或
ibex a mission that is remotely sensing
ibex 是一个 遥感 的任务
that boundary NASA also is preparing an
美国宇航局 也准备 了这个边界
additional mission the upcoming
即将到来的额外任务
interstellar mapping and acceleration
星际映射和加速度
probe or IMAP due to launch in 2024 to
探测器或IMAP 将于2024年发射至
capitalize on the voyagers observations
利用航海者的观察
while the probes have left the
而探针已经离开了
heliosphere Voyager 1 and Voyager 2 have
日光层旅行者号1和旅行者2号
not yet left the solar system and won't
还没有离开太阳系，也不会
be leaving anytime soon the boundary of
随时离开的边界
the solar system is considered to be
太阳系被认为是
beyond the outer edge of the Oort cloud
超越奥尔特云的外缘
a collection of small objects that are
一组小物件
still under the influence of the Sun's
仍然受到 太阳的 影响
gravity the width of the Oort cloud is
重力奥尔特云的宽度是
not known precisely but is estimated to
虽然不确切，但据估计
begin at about 1,000 astronomical units
从大约1,000个天文单位开始
or au from the Sun and to extend to
或来自太阳的au并延伸到
about 100,000 au 1 au is the distance
大约100,000 au 1 au是距离
from the Sun to the earth it will take
它将从太阳到地球
about three hundred years for Voyager 2
旅行者 2大约三 百年
to reach the inner edge of the Oort
到达 奥尔特的内边缘
cloud and possibly thirty thousand years
云可能三万年
to fly beyond it Voyager 2 launched in
飞越Voyager 2推出
1977 sixteen days before Voyager 1 and
1977年旅行者1号航行前十六天
both have traveled well beyond their
他们都远远超出了他们的
original destinations the spacecraft's
航天器的原始目的地
were built to last five years and
建造到五年了
conduct close-up studies of Jupiter and
对木星和木星进行特写研究
Saturn however as the mission continued
然而土星继续执行任务
additional flybys of the two outermost
两个最外面的额外飞行
giant planets Uranus and Neptune pollute
巨行星天王星和海王星污染
proved possible as the spacecraft flew
事实证明航天器飞行了
across the solar system
横跨太阳系
remote-controlled reprogramming was used
使用遥控重编程
to endow the voyagers with greater
赋予航海者更大的权利
capabilities than they possessed when
比他们拥有的能力
they left Earth their two planet mission
他们离开地球 他们的两个星球任务
became a four planet mission their five
他们的五个成为四个星球的任务
year life spans have stretched to 41
一年的寿命延长至41岁
years making voyager 2 nasa's
岁月做 旅行者2号美国宇航局
longest-running mission unbelievable
持续时间最长的任务令人难以置信
this is great this is we they definitely
这 是伟大的，这是我们他们肯定
did not picture this when they put the
他们放的时候并没有想到这一点
spacecraft up into the atmosphere right
飞船成大气 权
and here it is 41 years later blow in
这是41年后的事情
our minds unreal
我们的头脑不真实
was it once it reaches the Earth cloud
它曾经到达 地球云
that could happen I can't see it ever
这可能发生我无法看到它
going through but if it gets there we're
经历但是如果它到达那里我们就是
gonna start to see I I hope do we get to
要开始看到我希望我们能够到达
see pictures no does voyagers it's gonna
看到图片没有航海者会
be data it's gonna be data but but
是数据它会是 数据，但是
that's what I find so fascinating about
这就是我找到如此 着迷 约
this is that it was a five-year mission
这是一个 为期五年的任务
it's now 40 plus years into it the
它现在是40多年了
technology that's on Voyager 1 and 2 and
旅行者1号和2号旅行的技术
the data that's being transmitted is so
正在传输的数据是如此
archaic to what we use today but it's
我们 今天 使用的东西 已经 过时了， 但 它确实如此
still sending information we're like wow
还在发送信息我们就像哇
this is amazing I wish I had digital
这太棒了 我希望我有数字化
CMOS sensors back then oh yeah like
那时的 CMOS传感器哦，是的
could you like imagine the information
你能想象这些信息吗？
we would collect now if we were able to
如果我们能够 ， 我们现在会收集
but it's just it's neat that we're going
但它只是我们要走的很好
out we're still receiving the
我们仍然 收到了
information 16 hours later it's like
信息16小时之后就像是
sherry come on
雪利酒 来吧
but I will say totally you know just
但我会说你完全知道 刚才
Hollywood eyes the fact that it's still
好莱坞眼中的事实 是它仍然存在
going and you've got those Star Trek
去，你有 星际迷航
movies you know feature which one was
你知道哪部电影的功能
that
那
is that Star Trek 4 with the eternal
是星际迷航4与永恒
Series stuff the original oh it was so
系列东西原来哦它是如此
good but it makes me wonder one day if
好， 但它让我想知道 有一天
we get there are we gonna find these
我们到那里我们会找到这些
satellites crashed somewhere oh my
卫星在某处坠毁哦我的
goodness that's it that's how far it got
这就是它有多远
from oh now it's coming back to me Jeff
从哦，现在它回到我身边杰夫
I'm sure I saw that that's where the guy
我确定我看到那个人就是那个人
like saw that I forget his anybody's he
就像看到了 ，我忘了他的人是 他
like melds with the Spock no no not for
喜欢与Spock融为一体， 不是 没有
Sarah it's a crewman I forget
莎拉这是我忘了的船员
okay I don't know here since I've seen
好吧，自从我见过以后，我不知道这里
that yeah it's so cool
是的，这太酷了
in reality though yeah I mean away from
实际上，虽然是的，我的意思是远离
sci-fi videos of the the era like this
像这样的时代的科幻视频
is sensing data that is further away
正在感知更远的数据
from her than anything has ever been and
她比任何 以往任何时候都和
I think you know will the technology
我想你会知道这项技术
come that we can then surpass it like
来吧，我们可以超越它
we'll sure we send a probe that flies
我们肯定会发送一个飞行的探测器
well past Voyager 2 and says see yeah
远远超过旅行者2并且说 是的
I've got 16 megapixels in an array of
我有一个1600万像素的阵列
500 sensors and I'm gonna be taking some
500个传感器，我要拿 一些
pictures of this Earth cloud so it won't
这个 地球云的 图片 所以它不会
be missed a welcome they could create
错过他们可以创造的欢迎
another satellite to hit the trajectory
另一颗卫星击中了轨迹
path and go we're gonna like here's a
路径和去，我们会喜欢这里的
robotic whatever that's gonna install
机器人无论安装什么
other sensors on you and you know take
你知道的其他传感器
pictures of it yeah maybe rub some of
它的照片是啊也许 擦 一些
the the zebra mussels off it's something
斑马贻贝是它的东西
like that the interest to see if we have
喜欢看我们是否有兴趣
you know we could have the technology
你知道我们 可以 拥有这项技术
we're gonna we're gonna update you on
我们要告诉你们
the fly you know it's like a refueling
你知道这就像加油一样
spit in air just shoot it down it's been
在空中吐痰只是把它击落了
up there for a long time I just having a
在那里很长一段时间 我只有一个
five year lifespan and then being like
五年的生命，然后就像
extended to 41 years the poor Voyager 2
将可怜的旅行者2延长至41岁
is probably one can I retire how's the
可能 我 可以 退休 了
anti-malware on there think about that
反恶意软件在那里想想
how hackable is this device it's up
这台设备是多么可以破解它
there with technology from the 60s
那里有60年代的技术
exactly it's still very cool story
确切地说它仍然是非常酷的故事
big thanks to Roy W Nash in our
非常感谢Roy W Nash
community of viewers for submitting
观众社区提交
stories to us this week thanks for
本周故事给我们感谢
watching the category-five TV newsroom
看 五类电视 新闻编辑室
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
不要忘了喜欢和认购
all your tech news with a slight Linux
所有科技新闻都有轻微的 Linux
bias and for more free content be sure
偏见和更多免费内容确定
to check out our web site from the
从 检查出我们的 网站
category-five TV newsroom I'm Sasha
五类电视新闻编辑室我是Sasha
Rickman and I'm Robbie Ferguson and I'm
瑞克曼和我是罗比弗格森而我
Jeff Weston thank you once again for
杰夫韦斯顿再次感谢你
being here with us this week folks I
本周 与 我们在一起的 人们， 我
hope you had a great time I sure have
希望你有一个美好的时光，我肯定
and I look forward to being here with
我期待着在这里和
you again next weeks we'll see you
你下周我们会再见到你
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]